OxfordV2
  An app which processes the Oxford English Dictionary Researcher API, and exports to SuperMemo.

Usage:
  OxfordV2 [options] [<word>] [command]

Arguments:
  <word>  The word to look up. [default: mail]

Options:
  el, --etymology-language <etymology-language>  Restrict results to words derived from a certain language.  Languages are grouped by continent and hierarchical.  i.e. European will automatically include German.
  et, --etymology-type <etymology-type>          Restrict results only certain etymological types.  compound, derivative, conversion, blend, shortening, backformation, initialism, acronym, variant, arbitrary, imitative, borrowing, properName, unknown
  i, --interactive                               Open the interactive text menu features, where you can run follow-up queries, change options, and export queries. Has reduced features when compared to the command line.
  fq, --from-quote <from-quote>                  Get definitions for one of the quotes returned in the last search.  i.e. q 1 to get definitions for the first quote q 2-4 to loop-up definitions for quotes 2 through 4.
  ps, --part-of-speech <part-of-speech>          Only return results where the result relates to a specific part of speech (i.e. only nouns, only verbs)
  o, --obsolete-only                             Only return obsolete usages.
  oe, --obsolete-exclude                         Only return NON-obsolete usages.
  cf, --clear-export-file                        Delete the current export file.  The next time you export - you will start with a brand new file instead of continuing to append to the current file.
  sy, --start-year <start-year>                  Specify a start year. You can enter a range for a start year '-' i.e. 500-900
  ey, --end-year <end-year>                      Specify an end year. You can enter a range using a end year '-' i.e. 500-900
  p, --pronunciation                             Include IPA pronunciation with returned words. Both American and British.}
  pa, --pronunciation-usa                        Include American/USA IPA pronunciation with returned words.
  pb, --pronunciation-british                    Include British IPA pronunciation with returned words.
  e, --export                                    Export the results of this query.  Saved as XML for SuperMemo import. File will be saved as OED-export.xml
  y, --years <years>                             Years.  Use format 900-1999 or -1999 or 900-.  Used for first recorded, last recorded, and current in.
  c, --current-in                                Flag which sets the 'Years' option to work with current in year - as opposed to recorded in year - Restrict results to words current in this year or period. Works with the Years flag.  i.e. -y 280-1900 -c  another example: -y 500 -c will return the words current in the year 500 AD.
  r, --revised                                   Restrict words taken from new and revised OED entries (OED-3rd edition content)
  rn, --revised-not                              Restrict to non revised sources only. (OED 2nd and 1rst edition)
  q, --quotes                                    Return quotations for each word definition.  Use with export to make SuperMemo items where quotations are matched with their respective defintion.
  qs, --quotes-and-senses <Selection>            Return quotations for each sense definition.  Senses, and the quotations for each sense, are automatically matched.  Enter a selection as d1-3,15 or s1,3 etc. to get qs for a specific sense or definition.
  --version                                      Show version information
  -?, -h, --help                                 Show help and usage information

Commands:
  d, Derivatives, derivatives <selection>  Get derivatives for selected words.  Select which words returned by your last search, you would like to look up derivatives for. Enter the # of the last returned word you want to look up.  Works with range syntax as well (i.e. 1-9,11,15).  Works with the /word/{id}/derivatives endpoint. [default: ]
  Sense, sense                             Get senses for a word.  Takes a word id created by the last word search or simply enter a lemma after this command.
  Quote, quote                             Get quotations from the OED.  Get quotations based on a word or sense id (uses the last searched sense or word for the id).  Alternatively, you can search all quotations based on some parameters.
  Form, form <form>                        Get surfaceform records based on a word or passed word id.  A surfaceform record itemizes each of the specific orthographic forms that a word may take when it occurs in real-world text [default: peas]
  Semantic, semantic                       Search semantic classes.  Get related semantic classes based on sense id, branch, parent, ancestorys, children, siblings, descendants, etc.
  Lemma, lemma <text>                      Lemmatize text.  Enter a word or a string of words and return lemmas for each word or words.

q to exit.
>
No arguments entered
q to exit.
