<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<SuperMemoCollection>
  <Count>2</Count>
  <SuperMemoElement>
    <ID>1</ID>
    <Title>apple_nn01</Title>
    <Type>Item</Type>
    <Content>
      <Question>apple&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "On ðaes siwenigean eagum beoð ða aepplas hale, ac ða braewas greatigað,..oððaet sio scearpnes bið gewird ðaes aepples." --King Aelfred, 895&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "Ðurh ðone aepl ðaes eagan mon maeg geseon." --King Aelfred, 895&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "Mala punica, ða affricaniscan aeppla." --, 935&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "Spere, aepples." --, 935&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "Genim brembelaeppel &amp; elehtran &amp; pollegian, gecnua." --, 950&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "Se godcunda anwald gefrioðode his deorlingas under fiðra sceate, &amp; hi scilde swa geornlice swa man deð þone aeppel on his eagan." --King Aelfred, 950&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "Him mon on fruman þa mettas gife..swa swa beoþ aeppla, nales to swete ealles ac surmelsce, &amp; peran &amp; persucas." --, 950&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "Wudusuraeppel, fille &amp; finul, ealde sapan. Gewyrc ða wyrta to duste, maengc wiþ þa sapan &amp; wiþ þaes aepples gor." --, 1000&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "Aeppel unsaelga, þone hire aer forbead drihtna drihten, deaðbeames ofet." --, 1000&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "We haefdon cucumeres, þaet sind eorðaepla, &amp; pepones &amp; porleac &amp; enneleac &amp; manega oþre þingc." --, 1025&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "Worpað hine deofol on domdaege, draca egeslice, bismorlice, of blacere liðran irenum aplum." --, 1045&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "Geheald me, Drihten, and beorh me, swa swa man byrhð þam aeplum on his eagum mid his braewum." --King Aelfred, 1050&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "He..bið al swa is an eppel iheoweð." --, 1224&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "Eue bi heold oðe for boden appel." --, 1225&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "La prunele, the appel of the eye." --W. de Biblesworth, 1299&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "Þe Applene weren ripe inouȝ, riȝt ase it heruest were." --, 1300&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "Quane here apples ripe ben, fier-isles man mai ðor-inne sen." --, 1324&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "As he bi huld an hey, Vpe þe hexte bowe tweye applen he sey; &amp; þe bowes of þe on appel smite þe oþer vaste." --, 1325&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "Kepe me..as þe appel of þyn eȝe." --, 1350&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "Alle maner appul þat is closed in an harde skyn, rynde or schale is ycleped nux." --J. Trevisa, 1397&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "Þar-bi groues sum apell tre, Wit appuls selcut fair to se, Quen þai ar in hand, als a fise bal, To poudir wit a stink þai fal." --, 1399&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "Als appel ofe eghe yheme þou me." --, 1399&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "How adam brake goddis comandement of the appil." --, 1399&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "I prayed pieres to pulle adown an apple." --W. Langland, 1400&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "He was wont to holden a round appell of gold in his hond." --, 1424&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "Ȝe most forsake of golde ȝowre appil rounde Sceptre and swerde." --J. Lydgate, 1430&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "This tree..bringith forth soure applis." --R. Pecock, 1449&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "The delite of the apill l slow Eue." --, 1450&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "Take þe appullis of sypressus and ete hem or þe pouder of þe applys dryed." --, 1450&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "The Appyll of ye ee, pupilla." --, 1475&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "Yn the calendars of Ianuar' Thu sclatt treys both set &amp; rere To graffy ther yn appyl &amp; pere." --, 1499&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "Adam, oure alder, þat ete of þat appulle." --, 1499&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "These maner of people sell paradise for an apple, with Adam and Eue." --W. Bonde, 1526&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "Rough tasted appules are holsome where the stomake is weake." --T. Elyot, 1533&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "Venemous apples wherwith they poyson theyr arrowes." --R. Eden, 1555&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "To make ye apple of the chieck ruddy." --P. Morwyng, 1559&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "The Mandrake..beareth sayth Isidore, an Apple of sweete smell, which of some is called the Apple of the earth." --J. Maplet, 1567&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "What so euer fruite is to be eaten soft without, and hard within, is an Apple, and the contrary a Nut." --B. Googe, 1577&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "Takyng a branche of a Beeche a foote thicke: and when they haue cutte it and bored it, they set in it the branches of the best Peare or Apple that they can geat." --B. Googe, 1577&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "Giue him an Apple, or a Peare, or some such chyldes rewarde." --N. Breton, 1577&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "The knight kneeleth..with his naked sworde vnder his arme, the whiche beeing made of Iasper sprinkled with Uermilion spots, seemeth to be al bloudy, &amp; hee presenteth an apple of the same stone to the Princesse." --H. Wotton, 1578&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "If you touche him in the Indies, you touche the apple of his eye." --R. Hakluyt, 1584&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "We see our owne eies shine within the apples of our neighbours eies." --T. Bowes, 1586&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "The dart did undergore His eye-lid, by his eye's dear roots, &amp; out the apple fell." --G. Chapman, 1600&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "Hold a round ball or hollow apple of glasse." --P. Holland, 1601&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "Hereof commeth the colour Puniceus (i. a light red or a bay) taking the name of the apple Punicke or Pomegranate." --P. Holland, 1601&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "None have their eyes all of one color, for the bal or apple in the midst is ordinarily of another color than the white about." --P. Holland, 1601&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "that shall nourish no blood but your owne, tender your reputation as the apple of her eye, &amp; honour euen your verie footsteps." --E. Sharpham, 1607&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "The fruite or Apples of Palme-trees." --E. Topsell, 1607&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "Was it such a sinne for Adam to eate a forbidden Apple? Yes, the greatnes is remonstrable in the euent." --T. Adams, 1618&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "Oakes, Beeches, Chesnuts,..&amp;c. last longer than Apples, Peares, Plums, &amp;c." --F. Bacon, 1626&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "You that carried Summer in your lips..That in the Apples of your cheeks did wear A fertile Autumn now no fruit can bear?" --R. Heath, 1650&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "Syder is usually made of such Apples as are moist sommer fruits." --R. Austen, 1653&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "Graft..all kinds of Apples together, and also on Crabstocks." --R. Austen, 1653&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "The other trees gave no fruit; an uselesse apple from the Oak, or little berries from the Laurel and the Myrtle." --Bp. J. Taylor, 1660&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "They commonly mingle water in ye presse wth ye apples (a good quantity) whilst they grind ye apples." --J. Beale, 1663&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "Him by fraud I have seduc'd From his Creator..with an Apple." --J. Milton, 1667&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "He undertakes to Prove, that No Animal is generated but out of another Animal; Or some Plant Uncorrupted; as out of Oakapples, and severall prutuberancyes and Excresency's of Vegetables." --J. Finch, 1668&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "He can't live without you. You're the Apple of his Eye, the Joy of his Heart, the Lamp of his Life." --J. Bancroft, 1693&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "The apples call'd pompions by the Dutch,..grow scarce anywhere else in the Indies but in the Isle of Great Java." --, 1704&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "Shrugging up her Shoulders, to shew the tempting Apples of her white Breasts." --J. S., 1705&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "Having carefully observ'd the Eyes of several Fishes..I found that the..Pupil or Apple of the Eye, was very flat, like those in Human Creatures." --, 1705&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "Venders of..apples, plumbs." --R. Steele, 1712&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "An Apple, Pomum, is generally understood to be any fleshy Vessel containing more Seeds than one." --J. Martyn, 1729&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "You may also continue to prune Pears, Apples, and Plums until the middle or latter end of the next month." --P. Miller, 1731&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "The Vane on the Top of the Steeple is a Piece of fine Work..at the Extremity is a large gilded Apple or Globe." --W. Guthrie, 1743&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "To eat Meat that is forbidden, doth defile the Soul, as the Apple defiled Adam's." --J. J. Hornyold, 1749&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "He cut asunder the Apple of the eye in several animals." --, 1753&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "His daughter beautiful and young..The perfect picture of her mother's youth, His age's hope, the apple of his eye." --M. Bruce, 1766&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "The fly injects her juices into the oak leaf, to raise an apple for hatching her young." --A. Tucker, 1768&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "Fruit Trees thrive very well here, Apples Pears, Peaches, Plumbs Nectrans, Cherries Rasberries, &amp; Several other fine Fruit." --W. Bartram, 1774&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "Apples arrive to perfection for use..from July or August, until the end of October." --J. Abercrombie, 1779&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "A Venus, with the Wand or Hasta pura in one Hand, and the Golden Apple or Globe in the other." --W. Cooke, 1781&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "It is remarkable for producing great quantities of that delicious fruit we called apples." --J. Cook, 1784&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "Pomum or apple, which is a fleshy or pulpy kind of pericarpium: it contains in the middle a membraneous capsule..in which the seeds reside." --R. Saumarez, 1799&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "Most of our best apples are supposed to have been introduced into Britain by a fruiterer of Henry the Eighth." --H. Davy, 1813&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "The wood of France may be divided into six classes..for the fourth, fir, beech, elm, pear tree, apple, cherry tree." --, 1815&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "Poor Richard was to me as an eldest son, the apple of my eye." --W. Scott, 1816&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "The apple, though cultivated,..seems to be an exotic in southern Louisiana." --W. Darby, 1816&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "Dull people turn up..the apples of their eyes on beholding Prose by a Poet." --, 1827&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "The Apple had done but little for me If Eve had not done the rest." --R. Southey, 1829&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "The Custard-apples, Sweetsops, and Soursops, of the East and West Indies, are furnished by various species of Anona." --J. H. Balfour, 1849&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "Pear tree is superior in toughness to apple, but the latter excels sycamore and chestnut in hardness." --E. L. Tarbuck, 1857&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "Apple and Pears, stairs." --‘Ducange Anglicus’, 1857&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "Then came a course of fruits grown upon the place: luscious ‘Ripley’ Pine Apples and Star Apples (the latter..when cut across, displayed the seed chambers arranged in the exact form of a star)." --, 1858&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "Bedeguars, commonly called ‘Soft apples’. This name is given to Galls which are covered with numerous close-set hairs or fibres." --R. T. Hulme, 1861&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "He press'd His hand upon the apples of my breast." --‘Philocomus’, 1865&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "Mecca galls, Dead Sea apples, Sodom apples, or mad apples..are occasionally imported from Bussarah." --, 1869&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "Large dark blue sparkling eye..with much white, of a bluish shade, visible under the apple." --, 1870&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "You see, Eva, since Adam took the apple from Eve men have obeyed women nem. con." --H. B. Stowe, 1871&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "We count the apple as the King of fruits, because it is more generally known and used than any other." --F. R. Elliot, 1876&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "Col. Gildersleeve has lost his valuable setter dog Don, which animal was the apple of his eye." --, 1877&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "Of double-faced Canton flannel, finished with fringe and floss apples." --, 1881&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "He was a master of his profession, and his journal was to him as the apple of his eye." --, 1884&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "The pear may be budded on the thorn, the mountain ash, or the apple, but the practice is not to be recommended." --J. J. Black, 1887&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "The clock on the apples and pears Gave the office for us to clear." --, 1892&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "I saw the apple in his throat rise and fall with the effort he made to swallow." --S. J. Weyman, 1895&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "The other..does not form galls or ‘apples’, but the teleutospore masses break out directly from the stem." --, 1900&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "A gang of apple knockers strolled toward Mendon.., with Charles Dewey, the famous twirler." --, 1902&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "The woods used for turning are roughly divided into hard and soft... The latter include walnut, mahogany, oak, beech..and apple." --R. W. Cole, 1903&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "A friend of mine..recently bought a tract of land in Georgia, with a view to planting apples." --, 1907&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "It is a much-branched small tree or shrub, reaching a height of 6 meters, and is also known as the Punic apple." --N. L. Britton, 1908&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "Bill an' Jack's gone up apples." --J. R. Ware, 1909&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "The eye was also considered so as to elucidate the origin and application of such terms as bulb, apple, iris, pupil, cataract." --, 1912&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "Bert is playing a great game at third base and riding the old apple with wonderful severity." --, 1914&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "I soon shoved him down the Apples-and-pears." --C. Mackenzie, 1914&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "He looked..up and down the quay, a big apple bulging in his neck." --J. Joyce, 1922&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "Colours: Peach, Apple, Apricot, Mauve, Fuchsia, Periwinkle." --, 1923&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "Since man ate the apple..the human emotions are like a wedded wife." --D. H. Lawrence, 1924&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "No. 1711 has the smart ‘apple bowl’. A sporty looker, and a mighty friendly, comfortable pipe." --, 1926&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "‘I can't say,’ replied the poor apple." --S. J. Perelman, 1928&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "With what..delight did we children hover round our elders at night, while they gilded walnuts, or rubbed apples until they were as glossy as our own cheeks." --L. W. Reese, 1929&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "A section of the ‘potato apple’ is like that of the tomato." --, 1930&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "Live and die The apple, nay the onion, of his eye?" --R. Campbell, 1930&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "Jo-jo belts the old apple right through a high window." --D. Runyon, 1931&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "Apple, the big town, the main stem, Harlem." --C. Calloway, 1939&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "The Wild Apple has not the pyramidal form of the Wild Pear." --E. Step, 1940&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "In the Elizabethan era which, like the Hebraic and Christian, never recovered from the apple Eve gave Adam, woman was often a glorious strumpet." --A. Kreymborg, 1941&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "Boys do not meet with subdeb approval..are lumped together under such terms as..sad apples, meatballs,..and drips." --, 1941&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "Similar galls of a beautiful rose color develop sometimes on cranberries; they are called ‘rose apples’." --B. O. Dodge, 1943&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "If everything is running smoothly ‘she's apples’." --J. Binning, 1943&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "I love all the world And the movement of the apple in your throat." --C. Fry, 1946&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "Many thousands of tons of apples are wasted yearly." --, 1952&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "How's it going, Wally? Everything apples?" --T. A. G. Hungerford, 1952&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "I'll write you from the apple." --R. Ellison, 1953&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "The ‘Apple’ and the ‘Prince’ are examples of smaller, lighter bowls." --A. Dunhill, 1954&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "Andy picked up his two grenades... The apples felt strangely heavy in his hands." --M. Hargrove, 1956&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "Just you take a look at Jimmy here's eye..two circles there be, one for range and t'other for intelligence, and locked up in the apple, sir." --H. Williamson, 1957&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "When dry apple is one of the best woods for fuel." --M. Hadfield, 1957&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "She felt their faint movements of relief and surprise. ‘Well,’ said Dixon, ‘that'd be a break. That'd be apples, that would.’" --R. Stow, 1958&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "One of the removal men asked him if a sofa was to go ‘up the apples’." --J. G. Bennett, 1962&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "Don't cry, Pru. Yuh go and see old Len Ramsbottom and betcha everything'll be apples." --R. H. Morrieson, 1963&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "Her 8-year-old boy criticized her 10-year-old daughter by calling her an ‘apple.’" --, 1970&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "Mini dress..coffee, apple, rose or delphinium print on green." --, 1970&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "He lit a pipe, his largest shell-briar Apple." --M. J. Bosse, 1972&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "In 1883 Allen planted a mixture of Northern Spy, Baldwin and Rhode Island Greening apples." --, 1973&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "Both groups are symptomatic of the flood of young musicians storming into the Apple, abandoning studio sinecures and rock bands to play difficult improvisatory music." --G. Giddins, 1974&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "Thereafter the ‘imperial apple’ became an important emblem of the royal power invested in the monarch." --, 1974&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "No one reckons it's ‘apples’ in the battle for Bass." --, 1975&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "A peasant blouse that showed the top of those lovely little apples." --C. W. Smith, 1975&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "That's a different department; I don't hobnob with those apples." --R. P. Davis, 1976&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "She's apples. Now you just lie back an' take it easy." --R. Beilby, 1977&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "The ‘apples’, who categorically reject the Indian culture they were born to, choose one side, the white." --P. G. Allen, 1986&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "He parked his 1932 Mercedes-Benz (he called it the apple of his eye) outside A Block." --R. Mistry, 1987&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "Just when I raised my arms to throw to second, the damn apple slipped out of my hand." --R. A. Spears, 1989&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "He will use fruitwoods such as apple, plum, and, particularly, pear with its tight knit quality." --, 1990&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "Apples &amp; Rice, nice. Generally shortened to the first element when describing something that is nice, e.g. ‘She's apples’. But used in full when used to describe something that isn't, e.g., ‘Oh, that's very apples and rice. I'm out of work and you're pregnant again.’" --R. Puxley, 1992&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "Put one hand on the apple of the hound's throat and the other at the back of his head." --, 1992&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "Well, she's not much of a motor, but with a spray job and a new radiator she'll be apples!" --, 1994&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "You ain't shit, you fucking apple." --R. Hendrickson, 1994&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "Hand-carved pipes..including..a roughneck with an apple bowl for $18.95." --, 1994&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "Five minutes later, the same outfit again—this time in tangerine, then apple, then citrus." --, 1995&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "Errol was the apple of my grandmother's eye because he was her eldest." --P. Jooste, 1998&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "Apple, a classic pipe bowl shape resembling the roundness of an apple." --D. Wright, 2000&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "The hottest summer colours..include the dusted pastels of violet, poppy, apple,." --, 2000&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "I never saw money to do good things to Indians, it turns them into ‘Apples’—red on the outside, white in the middle." --, 2001&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "The oak gall, or oak-apple, was the source of the ink in many an old master drawing that is now falling to pieces." --, 2002&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "I'm glad Marbury is a Knick, but he sure does like to chuck that old apple, doesn't he?" --, 2004&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "Apply powder blush directly to the apple of the cheek." --, 2004&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "Leonard himself was a pretty tough apple." --, 2004&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "At this time the pupil of the eye was thought to be a solid object and was known as the apple because it was spherical." --, 2004&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "Some temperate trees (like apples and horse chestnuts) are pollinated by animals." --C. Tudge, 2005&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "I had inadvertently cut the branch of an overhanging manzanillo tree, whose apples are poison to humans." --, 2005&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "Many of the city's most creative people in the 1970s (as now) were high IQ boys and girls from Smalltown who fled to the Apple." --, 2005&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "The fear of Friday the 13th..is thought to have its origins in the Bible, as it was on a Friday when Eve took a bite from the apple." --, 2006&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "I fell down the apples and landed on me bottle." --, 2006&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "This handy apple corer/segmenter..will core and slice an apple into 12 even segments easily and simply." --, 2006&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "Those fellows are rotten apples." --G. H. Devol, 1887&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "There's no choosing between them rotten apples aft." --F. Riesenberg, 1918&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "Seen from this angle he looked what, in Bonaro's words he was,—‘a bad apple’." --R. Dougherty, 1962&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "The original ‘rotten apple’ is believed to have been a government agent." --L. Kennedy, 1980&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "You are the one that's going to be stuck with the bill if you pick a bad apple." --, 2006&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;</Question>
      <Answer>apple: The round firm fruit (a pome) of any of various wild and cultivated trees of the genus Malus (see sense 4a), occurring in a wide variety of forms, colours, and flavours; esp. any of numerous cultivated kinds produced throughout the temperate zones of both hemispheres, typically having crisp white flesh and green, yellow, or red skin.Noun.  Listed as a main definition. The original source of this word is listed as King Alfred. This word was first recored in 895</Answer>
      <SuperMemoReference>&amp;lt;H5 dir=ltr align=left&amp;gt;&amp;lt;Font size=&amp;quot;1&amp;quot; style=&amp;quot;color: transparent&amp;quot;&amp;gt; SuperMemo Reference:&amp;lt;/font&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;&amp;lt;FONT class=reference&amp;gt;Title:&amp;quot;My Test Quote&amp;quot; &amp;lt;br&amp;gt;Source: Oxford English Dictionary</SuperMemoReference>
    </Content>
  </SuperMemoElement>
  <SuperMemoElement>
    <ID>2</ID>
    <Title>apple_vb01</Title>
    <Type>Item</Type>
    <Content>
      <Question>apple&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "For all the sort of them during the Summer throughout, never rest and give over, but either they floure, or they apple, or els be readie to bring foorth fruit." --P. Holland, 1601&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "To Pome or Apple, is said of the Heads of Artichokes when they grow round, and full shaped as an Apple. It is said also of Lettuce, &amp;c." --J. Evelyn, 1693&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "Unless the Soil has some mixture of Sand the Turnips do not apple, as they call it: that is, do not bottom well." --J. Morton, 1712&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "The Turneps grew 'till Christmas or longer, and appled well in gravelly or stony Grounds, because their Roots can't here enter so deep." --W. Ellis, 1750&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "The cabbage turnep is of two kinds; one apples above ground, and the other in it." --C. Marshall, 1798&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "The poor people supply themselves with very good fuel by gathering the fir-apples and rotten wood; you will sometimes see twenty children in my plantations appleing, as they call it." --A. Young, 1799&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "Apple, to bottom at the roots. Turnips apple well, when the roots well, and assume a bulbous form." --A. E. Baker, 1854&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "The fine-leaved turnips that have escaped the fly, but have still to ‘apple’." --P. H. Emerson, 1895&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "Potatoes and onions are said to apple when they develop properly. A dialect use." --E. Gepp, 1923&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "Me taters be n't applin' like they ed ough'ter." --M. Carbery, 1948&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "Them blubs (bulbs) what we put awaay int' spring's gone an' appled nicely." --J. M. Sims-Kimbrey, 1995&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt; "Going out appling is going out into the woods to collect fir cones for burning." --J. M. Sims-Kimbrey, 1995&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;</Question>
      <Answer>apple: intransitive. Of vegetables, flower buds, and esp. (in later use) root crops: to swell into a globular shape; to become shaped like an apple.Verb.  Listed as a main definition. The original source of this word is listed as Philemon Holland. This word was first recored in 1601</Answer>
      <SuperMemoReference>&amp;lt;H5 dir=ltr align=left&amp;gt;&amp;lt;Font size=&amp;quot;1&amp;quot; style=&amp;quot;color: transparent&amp;quot;&amp;gt; SuperMemo Reference:&amp;lt;/font&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;&amp;lt;FONT class=reference&amp;gt;Title:&amp;quot;My Test Quote&amp;quot; &amp;lt;br&amp;gt;Source: Oxford English Dictionary</SuperMemoReference>
    </Content>
  </SuperMemoElement>
</SuperMemoCollection>