<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<SuperMemoCollection>
  <Count>368</Count>
  <SuperMemoElement>
    <ID>1</ID>
    <Title>apple_nn01-1</Title>
    <Type>Item</Type>
    <Content>
      <Question>Quotation #1On ðaes siwenigean eagum beoð ða aepplas hale, ac ða braewas greatigað,..oððaet sio scearpnes bið gewird ðaes aepples.&lt;BR&gt;King Aelfred, Pastoral Care &lt;BR&gt;895 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #2Ðurh ðone aepl ðaes eagan mon maeg geseon.&lt;BR&gt;King Aelfred, Pastoral Care &lt;BR&gt;895 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #3La prunele, the appel of the eye.&lt;BR&gt;W. de Biblesworth,  &lt;BR&gt;1299 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #4The Appyll of ye ee, pupilla.&lt;BR&gt;, Catholicon Anglicum &lt;BR&gt;1475 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #5We see our owne eies shine within the apples of our neighbours eies.&lt;BR&gt;T. Bowes, French Acad. &lt;BR&gt;1586 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #6The dart did undergore His eye-lid, by his eye's dear roots, &amp; out the apple fell.&lt;BR&gt;G. Chapman, Iliad &lt;BR&gt;1600 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #7None have their eyes all of one color, for the bal or apple in the midst is ordinarily of another color than the white about.&lt;BR&gt;P. Holland, Hist. World &lt;BR&gt;1601 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #8Having carefully observ'd the Eyes of several Fishes..I found that the..Pupil or Apple of the Eye, was very flat, like those in Human Creatures.&lt;BR&gt;, Philos. Trans. 1704–05 &lt;BR&gt;1705 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #9He cut asunder the Apple of the eye in several animals.&lt;BR&gt;, Chambers's Cycl. &lt;BR&gt;1753 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #10Dull people turn up..the apples of their eyes on beholding Prose by a Poet.&lt;BR&gt;, Blackwood's Edinb. Mag. &lt;BR&gt;1827 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #11Large dark blue sparkling eye..with much white, of a bluish shade, visible under the apple.&lt;BR&gt;, Anthropol. Rev. &lt;BR&gt;1870 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #12The eye was also considered so as to elucidate the origin and application of such terms as bulb, apple, iris, pupil, cataract.&lt;BR&gt;, Lancet &lt;BR&gt;1912 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #13Just you take a look at Jimmy here's eye..two circles there be, one for range and t'other for intelligence, and locked up in the apple, sir.&lt;BR&gt;H. Williamson, Golden Virgin &lt;BR&gt;1957 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #14At this time the pupil of the eye was thought to be a solid object and was known as the apple because it was spherical.&lt;BR&gt;, People &lt;BR&gt;2004 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;</Question>
      <Answer>The round firm fruit (a pome) of any of various wild and cultivated trees of the genus Malus (see sense 4a), occurring in a wide variety of forms, colours, and flavours; esp. any of numerous cultivated kinds produced throughout the temperate zones of both hemispheres, typically having crisp white flesh and green, yellow, or red skin. &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Sense #1 &lt;BR&gt;More fully apple of the eye. The pupil of the eye, originally thought to be a solid, spherical body. Occasionally also: the iris and pupil, or the whole eyeball. Now historical. &lt;BR&gt;First use: King Alfred &lt;BR&gt;Part of speech: NN &lt;BR&gt;895 -  &lt;BR&gt;</Answer>
      <SuperMemoReference>&amp;lt;H5 dir=ltr align=left&amp;gt;&amp;lt;Font size=&amp;quot;1&amp;quot; style=&amp;quot;color: transparent&amp;quot;&amp;gt; SuperMemo Reference:&amp;lt;/font&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;&amp;lt;FONT class=reference&amp;gt;Title:&amp;quot;My Test Quote&amp;quot; &amp;lt;br&amp;gt;Source: Oxford English Dictionary</SuperMemoReference>
    </Content>
  </SuperMemoElement>
  <SuperMemoElement>
    <ID>2</ID>
    <Title>apple_nn01-2</Title>
    <Type>Item</Type>
    <Content>
      <Question>Quotation #1Spere, aepples.&lt;BR&gt;, Cleopatra Gloss. &lt;BR&gt;935 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #2Worpað hine deofol on domdaege, draca egeslice, bismorlice, of blacere liðran irenum aplum.&lt;BR&gt;, Metrical Dialogue of Solomon &amp; Saturn &lt;BR&gt;1045 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #3He was wont to holden a round appell of gold in his hond.&lt;BR&gt;, Mandeville's Trav. &lt;BR&gt;1424 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #4Ȝe most forsake of golde ȝowre appil rounde Sceptre and swerde.&lt;BR&gt;J. Lydgate, Daunce Machabree &lt;BR&gt;1430 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #5To make ye apple of the chieck ruddy.&lt;BR&gt;P. Morwyng, Treasure of Euonymus &lt;BR&gt;1559 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #6The knight kneeleth..with his naked sworde vnder his arme, the whiche beeing made of Iasper sprinkled with Uermilion spots, seemeth to be al bloudy, &amp; hee presenteth an apple of the same stone to the Princesse.&lt;BR&gt;H. Wotton, Courtlie Controuersie &lt;BR&gt;1578 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #7Hold a round ball or hollow apple of glasse.&lt;BR&gt;P. Holland, Hist. World &lt;BR&gt;1601 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #8You that carried Summer in your lips..That in the Apples of your cheeks did wear A fertile Autumn now no fruit can bear?&lt;BR&gt;R. Heath, Clarastella &lt;BR&gt;1650 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #9Shrugging up her Shoulders, to shew the tempting Apples of her white Breasts.&lt;BR&gt;J. S., City &amp; Country Recreation &lt;BR&gt;1705 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #10The Vane on the Top of the Steeple is a Piece of fine Work..at the Extremity is a large gilded Apple or Globe.&lt;BR&gt;W. Guthrie, Trav. &lt;BR&gt;1743 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #11A Venus, with the Wand or Hasta pura in one Hand, and the Golden Apple or Globe in the other.&lt;BR&gt;W. Cooke, Medallic Hist. Imperial Rome &lt;BR&gt;1781 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #12He press'd His hand upon the apples of my breast.&lt;BR&gt;‘Philocomus’, Love Feast &lt;BR&gt;1865 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #13Of double-faced Canton flannel, finished with fringe and floss apples.&lt;BR&gt;, N.Y. Art Interchange &lt;BR&gt;1881 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #14Andy picked up his two grenades... The apples felt strangely heavy in his hands.&lt;BR&gt;M. Hargrove, Girl he left Behind &lt;BR&gt;1956 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #15Thereafter the ‘imperial apple’ became an important emblem of the royal power invested in the monarch.&lt;BR&gt;, Encycl. Brit. Macropaedia &lt;BR&gt;1974 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #16A peasant blouse that showed the top of those lovely little apples.&lt;BR&gt;C. W. Smith, Country Music &lt;BR&gt;1975 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #17Apply powder blush directly to the apple of the cheek.&lt;BR&gt;, Red &lt;BR&gt;2004 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;</Question>
      <Answer>The round firm fruit (a pome) of any of various wild and cultivated trees of the genus Malus (see sense 4a), occurring in a wide variety of forms, colours, and flavours; esp. any of numerous cultivated kinds produced throughout the temperate zones of both hemispheres, typically having crisp white flesh and green, yellow, or red skin. &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Sense #2 &lt;BR&gt;Any of various things resembling an apple in form or colour; spec. = pome n.1 2. &lt;BR&gt;First use: Cleopatra Glossary &lt;BR&gt;Part of speech: NN &lt;BR&gt;935 -  &lt;BR&gt;</Answer>
      <SuperMemoReference>&amp;lt;H5 dir=ltr align=left&amp;gt;&amp;lt;Font size=&amp;quot;1&amp;quot; style=&amp;quot;color: transparent&amp;quot;&amp;gt; SuperMemo Reference:&amp;lt;/font&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;&amp;lt;FONT class=reference&amp;gt;Title:&amp;quot;My Test Quote&amp;quot; &amp;lt;br&amp;gt;Source: Oxford English Dictionary</SuperMemoReference>
    </Content>
  </SuperMemoElement>
  <SuperMemoElement>
    <ID>3</ID>
    <Title>apple_nn01-3</Title>
    <Type>Item</Type>
    <Content>
      <Question>Quotation #1Mala punica, ða affricaniscan aeppla.&lt;BR&gt;, Cleopatra Gloss. &lt;BR&gt;935 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #2Genim brembelaeppel &amp; elehtran &amp; pollegian, gecnua.&lt;BR&gt;, Bald's Leechbk. &lt;BR&gt;950 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #3We haefdon cucumeres, þaet sind eorðaepla, &amp; pepones &amp; porleac &amp; enneleac &amp; manega oþre þingc.&lt;BR&gt;, Old Eng. Hexateuch: Num. &lt;BR&gt;1025 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #4Þe Applene weren ripe inouȝ, riȝt ase it heruest were.&lt;BR&gt;, St. Brendan &lt;BR&gt;1300 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #5Quane here apples ripe ben, fier-isles man mai ðor-inne sen.&lt;BR&gt;, Gen. &amp; Exod. &lt;BR&gt;1324 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #6Alle maner appul þat is closed in an harde skyn, rynde or schale is ycleped nux.&lt;BR&gt;J. Trevisa, De Proprietatibus Rerum &lt;BR&gt;1397 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #7Þar-bi groues sum apell tre, Wit appuls selcut fair to se, Quen þai ar in hand, als a fise bal, To poudir wit a stink þai fal.&lt;BR&gt;, Cursor Mundi &lt;BR&gt;1399 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #8Take þe appullis of sypressus and ete hem or þe pouder of þe applys dryed.&lt;BR&gt;, Practica Phisicalia John of Burgundy &lt;BR&gt;1450 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #9Venemous apples wherwith they poyson theyr arrowes.&lt;BR&gt;R. Eden, Decades of Newe Worlde &lt;BR&gt;1555 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #10The Mandrake..beareth sayth Isidore, an Apple of sweete smell, which of some is called the Apple of the earth.&lt;BR&gt;J. Maplet, Greene Forest &lt;BR&gt;1567 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #11Hereof commeth the colour Puniceus (i. a light red or a bay) taking the name of the apple Punicke or Pomegranate.&lt;BR&gt;P. Holland, Hist. World &lt;BR&gt;1601 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #12The fruite or Apples of Palme-trees.&lt;BR&gt;E. Topsell, Hist. Foure-footed Beastes &lt;BR&gt;1607 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #13The other trees gave no fruit; an uselesse apple from the Oak, or little berries from the Laurel and the Myrtle.&lt;BR&gt;Bp. J. Taylor, Worthy Communicant &lt;BR&gt;1660 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #14The apples call'd pompions by the Dutch,..grow scarce anywhere else in the Indies but in the Isle of Great Java.&lt;BR&gt;, Voy. E.-Indies &lt;BR&gt;1704 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #15It is remarkable for producing great quantities of that delicious fruit we called apples.&lt;BR&gt;J. Cook, Voy. Pacific &lt;BR&gt;1784 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #16The Custard-apples, Sweetsops, and Soursops, of the East and West Indies, are furnished by various species of Anona.&lt;BR&gt;J. H. Balfour, Man. Bot. &lt;BR&gt;1849 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #17Then came a course of fruits grown upon the place: luscious ‘Ripley’ Pine Apples and Star Apples (the latter..when cut across, displayed the seed chambers arranged in the exact form of a star).&lt;BR&gt;, Harper's Mag. &lt;BR&gt;1858 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #18It is a much-branched small tree or shrub, reaching a height of 6 meters, and is also known as the Punic apple.&lt;BR&gt;N. L. Britton, N. Amer. Trees &lt;BR&gt;1908 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #19A section of the ‘potato apple’ is like that of the tomato.&lt;BR&gt;, Times Educ. Suppl. &lt;BR&gt;1930 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #20I had inadvertently cut the branch of an overhanging manzanillo tree, whose apples are poison to humans.&lt;BR&gt;, Smithsonian &lt;BR&gt;2005 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;</Question>
      <Answer>The round firm fruit (a pome) of any of various wild and cultivated trees of the genus Malus (see sense 4a), occurring in a wide variety of forms, colours, and flavours; esp. any of numerous cultivated kinds produced throughout the temperate zones of both hemispheres, typically having crisp white flesh and green, yellow, or red skin. &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Sense #3 &lt;BR&gt;Frequently with distinguishing word: any of various fruits (and vegetables), esp. those thought to resemble the apple (sense 1) in some way; any of the plants producing such a fruit (or vegetable). &lt;BR&gt;First use: Cleopatra Glossary &lt;BR&gt;Part of speech: NN &lt;BR&gt;935 -  &lt;BR&gt;</Answer>
      <SuperMemoReference>&amp;lt;H5 dir=ltr align=left&amp;gt;&amp;lt;Font size=&amp;quot;1&amp;quot; style=&amp;quot;color: transparent&amp;quot;&amp;gt; SuperMemo Reference:&amp;lt;/font&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;&amp;lt;FONT class=reference&amp;gt;Title:&amp;quot;My Test Quote&amp;quot; &amp;lt;br&amp;gt;Source: Oxford English Dictionary</SuperMemoReference>
    </Content>
  </SuperMemoElement>
  <SuperMemoElement>
    <ID>4</ID>
    <Title>apple_nn01-4</Title>
    <Type>Item</Type>
    <Content>
      <Question>Quotation #1Se godcunda anwald gefrioðode his deorlingas under fiðra sceate, &amp; hi scilde swa geornlice swa man deð þone aeppel on his eagan.&lt;BR&gt;King Aelfred, De Consol. Philos. &lt;BR&gt;950 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #2Geheald me, Drihten, and beorh me, swa swa man byrhð þam aeplum on his eagum mid his braewum.&lt;BR&gt;King Aelfred, Psalms &lt;BR&gt;1050 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #3Kepe me..as þe appel of þyn eȝe.&lt;BR&gt;, Psalter &lt;BR&gt;1350 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #4Als appel ofe eghe yheme þou me.&lt;BR&gt;, Psalter &lt;BR&gt;1399 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #5If you touche him in the Indies, you touche the apple of his eye.&lt;BR&gt;R. Hakluyt, Disc. Western Planting &lt;BR&gt;1584 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #6that shall nourish no blood but your owne, tender your reputation as the apple of her eye, &amp; honour euen your verie footsteps.&lt;BR&gt;E. Sharpham, Cupids Whirligig &lt;BR&gt;1607 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #7He can't live without you. You're the Apple of his Eye, the Joy of his Heart, the Lamp of his Life.&lt;BR&gt;J. Bancroft, Henry II &lt;BR&gt;1693 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #8His daughter beautiful and young..The perfect picture of her mother's youth, His age's hope, the apple of his eye.&lt;BR&gt;M. Bruce, Poems &lt;BR&gt;1766 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #9Poor Richard was to me as an eldest son, the apple of my eye.&lt;BR&gt;W. Scott, Old Mortality &lt;BR&gt;1816 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #10Col. Gildersleeve has lost his valuable setter dog Don, which animal was the apple of his eye.&lt;BR&gt;, Spirit of Times &lt;BR&gt;1877 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #11He was a master of his profession, and his journal was to him as the apple of his eye.&lt;BR&gt;, Harper's Mag. &lt;BR&gt;1884 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #12Live and die The apple, nay the onion, of his eye?&lt;BR&gt;R. Campbell, Poems &lt;BR&gt;1930 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #13He parked his 1932 Mercedes-Benz (he called it the apple of his eye) outside A Block.&lt;BR&gt;R. Mistry, Tales from Firozsha Baag &lt;BR&gt;1987 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #14Errol was the apple of my grandmother's eye because he was her eldest.&lt;BR&gt;P. Jooste, Dance with Poor Man's Daughter &lt;BR&gt;1998 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;</Question>
      <Answer>The round firm fruit (a pome) of any of various wild and cultivated trees of the genus Malus (see sense 4a), occurring in a wide variety of forms, colours, and flavours; esp. any of numerous cultivated kinds produced throughout the temperate zones of both hemispheres, typically having crisp white flesh and green, yellow, or red skin. &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Sense #4 &lt;BR&gt;More fully apple of the eye. figurative and in extended use. Originally: the type of something precious. In later use chiefly the apple of a person's eye: the particular object of a person's affection or regard; a greatly cherished person or occasionally thing. &lt;BR&gt;First use: King Alfred &lt;BR&gt;Part of speech: NN &lt;BR&gt;950 -  &lt;BR&gt;</Answer>
      <SuperMemoReference>&amp;lt;H5 dir=ltr align=left&amp;gt;&amp;lt;Font size=&amp;quot;1&amp;quot; style=&amp;quot;color: transparent&amp;quot;&amp;gt; SuperMemo Reference:&amp;lt;/font&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;&amp;lt;FONT class=reference&amp;gt;Title:&amp;quot;My Test Quote&amp;quot; &amp;lt;br&amp;gt;Source: Oxford English Dictionary</SuperMemoReference>
    </Content>
  </SuperMemoElement>
  <SuperMemoElement>
    <ID>5</ID>
    <Title>apple_nn01-5</Title>
    <Type>Item</Type>
    <Content>
      <Question>Quotation #1Him mon on fruman þa mettas gife..swa swa beoþ aeppla, nales to swete ealles ac surmelsce, &amp; peran &amp; persucas.&lt;BR&gt;, Bald's Leechbk. &lt;BR&gt;950 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #2Wudusuraeppel, fille &amp; finul, ealde sapan. Gewyrc ða wyrta to duste, maengc wiþ þa sapan &amp; wiþ þaes aepples gor.&lt;BR&gt;, Metrical Charm: Nine Herbs &lt;BR&gt;1000 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #3He..bið al swa is an eppel iheoweð.&lt;BR&gt;, MS Lamb. &lt;BR&gt;1224 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #4As he bi huld an hey, Vpe þe hexte bowe tweye applen he sey; &amp; þe bowes of þe on appel smite þe oþer vaste.&lt;BR&gt;, Chron. Robert of Gloucester &lt;BR&gt;1325 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #5I prayed pieres to pulle adown an apple.&lt;BR&gt;W. Langland, Piers Plowman &lt;BR&gt;1400 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #6This tree..bringith forth soure applis.&lt;BR&gt;R. Pecock, Repressor &lt;BR&gt;1449 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #7Rough tasted appules are holsome where the stomake is weake.&lt;BR&gt;T. Elyot, Castel of Helthe &lt;BR&gt;1533 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #8Giue him an Apple, or a Peare, or some such chyldes rewarde.&lt;BR&gt;N. Breton, Floorish vpon Fancie &lt;BR&gt;1577 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #9Syder is usually made of such Apples as are moist sommer fruits.&lt;BR&gt;R. Austen, Treat. Fruit-trees &lt;BR&gt;1653 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #10They commonly mingle water in ye presse wth ye apples (a good quantity) whilst they grind ye apples.&lt;BR&gt;J. Beale, Let. &lt;BR&gt;1663 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #11Venders of..apples, plumbs.&lt;BR&gt;R. Steele, Spectator &lt;BR&gt;1712 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #12Apples arrive to perfection for use..from July or August, until the end of October.&lt;BR&gt;J. Abercrombie, Brit. Fruit-gardener &lt;BR&gt;1779 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #13Most of our best apples are supposed to have been introduced into Britain by a fruiterer of Henry the Eighth.&lt;BR&gt;H. Davy, Elements Agric. Chem. &lt;BR&gt;1813 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #14We count the apple as the King of fruits, because it is more generally known and used than any other.&lt;BR&gt;F. R. Elliot, Hand-bk. for Fruit Growers &lt;BR&gt;1876 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #15With what..delight did we children hover round our elders at night, while they gilded walnuts, or rubbed apples until they were as glossy as our own cheeks.&lt;BR&gt;L. W. Reese, Victorian Village &lt;BR&gt;1929 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #16Many thousands of tons of apples are wasted yearly.&lt;BR&gt;, Times &lt;BR&gt;1952 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #17This handy apple corer/segmenter..will core and slice an apple into 12 even segments easily and simply.&lt;BR&gt;, Weight Watchers Mag. &lt;BR&gt;2006 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;</Question>
      <Answer>The round firm fruit (a pome) of any of various wild and cultivated trees of the genus Malus (see sense 4a), occurring in a wide variety of forms, colours, and flavours; esp. any of numerous cultivated kinds produced throughout the temperate zones of both hemispheres, typically having crisp white flesh and green, yellow, or red skin. &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Sense #5 &lt;BR&gt;The round firm fruit (a pome) of any of various wild and cultivated trees of the genus Malus (see sense 4a), occurring in a wide variety of forms, colours, and flavours; esp. any of numerous cultivated kinds produced throughout the temperate zones of both hemispheres, typically having crisp white flesh and green, yellow, or red skin. &lt;BR&gt;First use: Bald's Leechbook &lt;BR&gt;Part of speech: NN &lt;BR&gt;950 -  &lt;BR&gt;This is the main current sense &lt;BR&gt;</Answer>
      <SuperMemoReference>&amp;lt;H5 dir=ltr align=left&amp;gt;&amp;lt;Font size=&amp;quot;1&amp;quot; style=&amp;quot;color: transparent&amp;quot;&amp;gt; SuperMemo Reference:&amp;lt;/font&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;&amp;lt;FONT class=reference&amp;gt;Title:&amp;quot;My Test Quote&amp;quot; &amp;lt;br&amp;gt;Source: Oxford English Dictionary</SuperMemoReference>
    </Content>
  </SuperMemoElement>
  <SuperMemoElement>
    <ID>6</ID>
    <Title>apple_nn01-6</Title>
    <Type>Item</Type>
    <Content>
      <Question>Quotation #1Aeppel unsaelga, þone hire aer forbead drihtna drihten, deaðbeames ofet.&lt;BR&gt;, Genesis B &lt;BR&gt;1000 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #2Eue bi heold oðe for boden appel.&lt;BR&gt;, Ancrene Riwle &lt;BR&gt;1225 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #3How adam brake goddis comandement of the appil.&lt;BR&gt;, Cursor Mundi &lt;BR&gt;1399 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #4The delite of the apill l slow Eue.&lt;BR&gt;, Bk. Knight of La Tour Landry &lt;BR&gt;1450 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #5Adam, oure alder, þat ete of þat appulle.&lt;BR&gt;, St. Erkenwald &lt;BR&gt;1499 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #6These maner of people sell paradise for an apple, with Adam and Eue.&lt;BR&gt;W. Bonde, Pylgrimage of Perfection &lt;BR&gt;1526 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #7Was it such a sinne for Adam to eate a forbidden Apple? Yes, the greatnes is remonstrable in the euent.&lt;BR&gt;T. Adams, Happines of Church &lt;BR&gt;1618 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #8Him by fraud I have seduc'd From his Creator..with an Apple.&lt;BR&gt;J. Milton, Paradise Lost &lt;BR&gt;1667 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #9To eat Meat that is forbidden, doth defile the Soul, as the Apple defiled Adam's.&lt;BR&gt;J. J. Hornyold, Real Princ. Catholicks &lt;BR&gt;1749 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #10The Apple had done but little for me If Eve had not done the rest.&lt;BR&gt;R. Southey, All for Love &lt;BR&gt;1829 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #11You see, Eva, since Adam took the apple from Eve men have obeyed women nem. con.&lt;BR&gt;H. B. Stowe, My Wife &amp; I &lt;BR&gt;1871 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #12Since man ate the apple..the human emotions are like a wedded wife.&lt;BR&gt;D. H. Lawrence, Phoenix &lt;BR&gt;1924 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #13In the Elizabethan era which, like the Hebraic and Christian, never recovered from the apple Eve gave Adam, woman was often a glorious strumpet.&lt;BR&gt;A. Kreymborg, Poetic Drama &lt;BR&gt;1941 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #14The fear of Friday the 13th..is thought to have its origins in the Bible, as it was on a Friday when Eve took a bite from the apple.&lt;BR&gt;, Daily Mail &lt;BR&gt;2006 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;</Question>
      <Answer>The round firm fruit (a pome) of any of various wild and cultivated trees of the genus Malus (see sense 4a), occurring in a wide variety of forms, colours, and flavours; esp. any of numerous cultivated kinds produced throughout the temperate zones of both hemispheres, typically having crisp white flesh and green, yellow, or red skin. &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Sense #6 &lt;BR&gt;According to post-biblical Christian tradition: the fruit of the tree of knowledge of good and evil eaten by Adam and Eve in the Garden of Eden in defiance of God's commandment; the forbidden fruit. Also used allusively. &lt;BR&gt;First use: Genesis B &lt;BR&gt;Part of speech: NN &lt;BR&gt;1000 -  &lt;BR&gt;</Answer>
      <SuperMemoReference>&amp;lt;H5 dir=ltr align=left&amp;gt;&amp;lt;Font size=&amp;quot;1&amp;quot; style=&amp;quot;color: transparent&amp;quot;&amp;gt; SuperMemo Reference:&amp;lt;/font&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;&amp;lt;FONT class=reference&amp;gt;Title:&amp;quot;My Test Quote&amp;quot; &amp;lt;br&amp;gt;Source: Oxford English Dictionary</SuperMemoReference>
    </Content>
  </SuperMemoElement>
  <SuperMemoElement>
    <ID>7</ID>
    <Title>apple_nn01-7</Title>
    <Type>Item</Type>
    <Content>
      <Question>Quotation #1Yn the calendars of Ianuar' Thu sclatt treys both set &amp; rere To graffy ther yn appyl &amp; pere.&lt;BR&gt;, Treat. Gardening &lt;BR&gt;1499 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #2Takyng a branche of a Beeche a foote thicke: and when they haue cutte it and bored it, they set in it the branches of the best Peare or Apple that they can geat.&lt;BR&gt;B. Googe, Foure Bks. Husbandry &lt;BR&gt;1577 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #3Oakes, Beeches, Chesnuts,..&amp;c. last longer than Apples, Peares, Plums, &amp;c.&lt;BR&gt;F. Bacon, Sylua Syluarum &lt;BR&gt;1626 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #4Graft..all kinds of Apples together, and also on Crabstocks.&lt;BR&gt;R. Austen, Treat. Fruit-trees &lt;BR&gt;1653 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #5You may also continue to prune Pears, Apples, and Plums until the middle or latter end of the next month.&lt;BR&gt;P. Miller, Gardeners Kalendar &lt;BR&gt;1731 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #6Fruit Trees thrive very well here, Apples Pears, Peaches, Plumbs Nectrans, Cherries Rasberries, &amp; Several other fine Fruit.&lt;BR&gt;W. Bartram, Trav. Georgia &amp; Florida &lt;BR&gt;1774 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #7The apple, though cultivated,..seems to be an exotic in southern Louisiana.&lt;BR&gt;W. Darby, Geogr. Descr. Louisiana &lt;BR&gt;1816 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #8The pear may be budded on the thorn, the mountain ash, or the apple, but the practice is not to be recommended.&lt;BR&gt;J. J. Black, Cultiv. Peach &amp; Pear &lt;BR&gt;1887 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #9A friend of mine..recently bought a tract of land in Georgia, with a view to planting apples.&lt;BR&gt;, Times &lt;BR&gt;1907 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #10The Wild Apple has not the pyramidal form of the Wild Pear.&lt;BR&gt;E. Step, Wayside &amp; Woodland Trees &lt;BR&gt;1940 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #11In 1883 Allen planted a mixture of Northern Spy, Baldwin and Rhode Island Greening apples.&lt;BR&gt;, Vermont Life &lt;BR&gt;1973 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #12Some temperate trees (like apples and horse chestnuts) are pollinated by animals.&lt;BR&gt;C. Tudge, Secret Life Trees &lt;BR&gt;2005 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;</Question>
      <Answer>The round firm fruit (a pome) of any of various wild and cultivated trees of the genus Malus (see sense 4a), occurring in a wide variety of forms, colours, and flavours; esp. any of numerous cultivated kinds produced throughout the temperate zones of both hemispheres, typically having crisp white flesh and green, yellow, or red skin. &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Sense #7 &lt;BR&gt;Any tree of the genus Malus (family Rosaceae); esp. any of the numerous varieties cultivated for their fruit, probably of hybrid origin and usually classified as M. domestica, having alternate serrated leaves and white blossom appearing in the spring, followed by fruit in late summer or autumn. Cf. apple tree n. &lt;BR&gt;First use: Treat. Gardening &lt;BR&gt;Part of speech: NN &lt;BR&gt;1499 -  &lt;BR&gt;</Answer>
      <SuperMemoReference>&amp;lt;H5 dir=ltr align=left&amp;gt;&amp;lt;Font size=&amp;quot;1&amp;quot; style=&amp;quot;color: transparent&amp;quot;&amp;gt; SuperMemo Reference:&amp;lt;/font&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;&amp;lt;FONT class=reference&amp;gt;Title:&amp;quot;My Test Quote&amp;quot; &amp;lt;br&amp;gt;Source: Oxford English Dictionary</SuperMemoReference>
    </Content>
  </SuperMemoElement>
  <SuperMemoElement>
    <ID>8</ID>
    <Title>apple_nn01-8</Title>
    <Type>Item</Type>
    <Content>
      <Question>Quotation #1What so euer fruite is to be eaten soft without, and hard within, is an Apple, and the contrary a Nut.&lt;BR&gt;B. Googe, Foure Bks. Husbandry &lt;BR&gt;1577 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #2An Apple, Pomum, is generally understood to be any fleshy Vessel containing more Seeds than one.&lt;BR&gt;J. Martyn, 1st Lect. Bot. &lt;BR&gt;1729 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #3Pomum or apple, which is a fleshy or pulpy kind of pericarpium: it contains in the middle a membraneous capsule..in which the seeds reside.&lt;BR&gt;R. Saumarez, New Syst. Physiol. &lt;BR&gt;1799 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;</Question>
      <Answer>The round firm fruit (a pome) of any of various wild and cultivated trees of the genus Malus (see sense 4a), occurring in a wide variety of forms, colours, and flavours; esp. any of numerous cultivated kinds produced throughout the temperate zones of both hemispheres, typically having crisp white flesh and green, yellow, or red skin. &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Sense #8 &lt;BR&gt;Botany. Any fruit having the structure of the apple; a pome. Obsolete. &lt;BR&gt;First use: Barnabe Googe &lt;BR&gt;Part of speech: NN &lt;BR&gt;1577 - 1799 &lt;BR&gt;This sense is obsolete &lt;BR&gt;</Answer>
      <SuperMemoReference>&amp;lt;H5 dir=ltr align=left&amp;gt;&amp;lt;Font size=&amp;quot;1&amp;quot; style=&amp;quot;color: transparent&amp;quot;&amp;gt; SuperMemo Reference:&amp;lt;/font&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;&amp;lt;FONT class=reference&amp;gt;Title:&amp;quot;My Test Quote&amp;quot; &amp;lt;br&amp;gt;Source: Oxford English Dictionary</SuperMemoReference>
    </Content>
  </SuperMemoElement>
  <SuperMemoElement>
    <ID>9</ID>
    <Title>apple_nn01-9</Title>
    <Type>Item</Type>
    <Content>
      <Question>Quotation #1He undertakes to Prove, that No Animal is generated but out of another Animal; Or some Plant Uncorrupted; as out of Oakapples, and severall prutuberancyes and Excresency's of Vegetables.&lt;BR&gt;J. Finch, Let. &lt;BR&gt;1668 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #2The fly injects her juices into the oak leaf, to raise an apple for hatching her young.&lt;BR&gt;A. Tucker, Light of Nature Pursued &lt;BR&gt;1768 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #3Bedeguars, commonly called ‘Soft apples’. This name is given to Galls which are covered with numerous close-set hairs or fibres.&lt;BR&gt;R. T. Hulme, Elements Med. Zool. &lt;BR&gt;1861 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #4Mecca galls, Dead Sea apples, Sodom apples, or mad apples..are occasionally imported from Bussarah.&lt;BR&gt;, Eng. Mech. &lt;BR&gt;1869 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #5The other..does not form galls or ‘apples’, but the teleutospore masses break out directly from the stem.&lt;BR&gt;, Bull. Torrey Bot. Club &lt;BR&gt;1900 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #6Similar galls of a beautiful rose color develop sometimes on cranberries; they are called ‘rose apples’.&lt;BR&gt;B. O. Dodge, Dis. &amp; Pests of Ornamental Plants &lt;BR&gt;1943 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #7The oak gall, or oak-apple, was the source of the ink in many an old master drawing that is now falling to pieces.&lt;BR&gt;, N.Y. Rev. Bks. &lt;BR&gt;2002 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;</Question>
      <Answer>The round firm fruit (a pome) of any of various wild and cultivated trees of the genus Malus (see sense 4a), occurring in a wide variety of forms, colours, and flavours; esp. any of numerous cultivated kinds produced throughout the temperate zones of both hemispheres, typically having crisp white flesh and green, yellow, or red skin. &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Sense #9 &lt;BR&gt;Chiefly with distinguishing word: a gall on the stem or leaf of a plant. &lt;BR&gt;First use: J. Finch &lt;BR&gt;Part of speech: NN &lt;BR&gt;1668 -  &lt;BR&gt;</Answer>
      <SuperMemoReference>&amp;lt;H5 dir=ltr align=left&amp;gt;&amp;lt;Font size=&amp;quot;1&amp;quot; style=&amp;quot;color: transparent&amp;quot;&amp;gt; SuperMemo Reference:&amp;lt;/font&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;&amp;lt;FONT class=reference&amp;gt;Title:&amp;quot;My Test Quote&amp;quot; &amp;lt;br&amp;gt;Source: Oxford English Dictionary</SuperMemoReference>
    </Content>
  </SuperMemoElement>
  <SuperMemoElement>
    <ID>10</ID>
    <Title>apple_nn01-10</Title>
    <Type>Item</Type>
    <Content>
      <Question>Quotation #1The wood of France may be divided into six classes..for the fourth, fir, beech, elm, pear tree, apple, cherry tree.&lt;BR&gt;, Edinb. Encycl. &lt;BR&gt;1815 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #2Pear tree is superior in toughness to apple, but the latter excels sycamore and chestnut in hardness.&lt;BR&gt;E. L. Tarbuck, Encycl. Pract. Carpentry &amp; Joinery &lt;BR&gt;1857 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #3The woods used for turning are roughly divided into hard and soft... The latter include walnut, mahogany, oak, beech..and apple.&lt;BR&gt;R. W. Cole,  &lt;BR&gt;1903 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #4When dry apple is one of the best woods for fuel.&lt;BR&gt;M. Hadfield, Brit. Trees &lt;BR&gt;1957 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #5He will use fruitwoods such as apple, plum, and, particularly, pear with its tight knit quality.&lt;BR&gt;, Woodworker &lt;BR&gt;1990 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;</Question>
      <Answer>The round firm fruit (a pome) of any of various wild and cultivated trees of the genus Malus (see sense 4a), occurring in a wide variety of forms, colours, and flavours; esp. any of numerous cultivated kinds produced throughout the temperate zones of both hemispheres, typically having crisp white flesh and green, yellow, or red skin. &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Sense #10 &lt;BR&gt;The wood of any of these trees, esp. used in woodworking. Cf. apple-wood n. at  compounds 1a(a). &lt;BR&gt;First use: Edinburgh Encyclopaedia &lt;BR&gt;Part of speech: NN &lt;BR&gt;1815 -  &lt;BR&gt;</Answer>
      <SuperMemoReference>&amp;lt;H5 dir=ltr align=left&amp;gt;&amp;lt;Font size=&amp;quot;1&amp;quot; style=&amp;quot;color: transparent&amp;quot;&amp;gt; SuperMemo Reference:&amp;lt;/font&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;&amp;lt;FONT class=reference&amp;gt;Title:&amp;quot;My Test Quote&amp;quot; &amp;lt;br&amp;gt;Source: Oxford English Dictionary</SuperMemoReference>
    </Content>
  </SuperMemoElement>
  <SuperMemoElement>
    <ID>11</ID>
    <Title>apple_nn01-11</Title>
    <Type>Item</Type>
    <Content>
      <Question>Quotation #1Apple and Pears, stairs.&lt;BR&gt;‘Ducange Anglicus’, Vulgar Tongue &lt;BR&gt;1857 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #2The clock on the apples and pears Gave the office for us to clear.&lt;BR&gt;, Sporting Times &lt;BR&gt;1892 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #3Bill an' Jack's gone up apples.&lt;BR&gt;J. R. Ware, Passing Eng. Victorian Era &lt;BR&gt;1909 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #4I soon shoved him down the Apples-and-pears.&lt;BR&gt;C. Mackenzie, Sinister St. &lt;BR&gt;1914 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #5One of the removal men asked him if a sofa was to go ‘up the apples’.&lt;BR&gt;J. G. Bennett, Witness &lt;BR&gt;1962 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #6I fell down the apples and landed on me bottle.&lt;BR&gt;, Forward &lt;BR&gt;2006 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;</Question>
      <Answer>The round firm fruit (a pome) of any of various wild and cultivated trees of the genus Malus (see sense 4a), occurring in a wide variety of forms, colours, and flavours; esp. any of numerous cultivated kinds produced throughout the temperate zones of both hemispheres, typically having crisp white flesh and green, yellow, or red skin. &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Sense #11 &lt;BR&gt;In full apple(s) and pears. Stairs. &lt;BR&gt;First use: ‘Ducange Anglicus’ &lt;BR&gt;Part of speech: NN &lt;BR&gt;1857 -  &lt;BR&gt;</Answer>
      <SuperMemoReference>&amp;lt;H5 dir=ltr align=left&amp;gt;&amp;lt;Font size=&amp;quot;1&amp;quot; style=&amp;quot;color: transparent&amp;quot;&amp;gt; SuperMemo Reference:&amp;lt;/font&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;&amp;lt;FONT class=reference&amp;gt;Title:&amp;quot;My Test Quote&amp;quot; &amp;lt;br&amp;gt;Source: Oxford English Dictionary</SuperMemoReference>
    </Content>
  </SuperMemoElement>
  <SuperMemoElement>
    <ID>12</ID>
    <Title>apple_nn01-12</Title>
    <Type>Item</Type>
    <Content>
      <Question>Quotation #1Those fellows are rotten apples.&lt;BR&gt;G. H. Devol, Forty Years Gambler on Mississippi &lt;BR&gt;1887 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #2There's no choosing between them rotten apples aft.&lt;BR&gt;F. Riesenberg, Under Sail &lt;BR&gt;1918 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #3Seen from this angle he looked what, in Bonaro's words he was,—‘a bad apple’.&lt;BR&gt;R. Dougherty, Commissioner &lt;BR&gt;1962 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #4The original ‘rotten apple’ is believed to have been a government agent.&lt;BR&gt;L. Kennedy, Brit. Intelligence Services in Action &lt;BR&gt;1980 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #5You are the one that's going to be stuck with the bill if you pick a bad apple.&lt;BR&gt;, Detroit News &lt;BR&gt;2006 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;</Question>
      <Answer>The round firm fruit (a pome) of any of various wild and cultivated trees of the genus Malus (see sense 4a), occurring in a wide variety of forms, colours, and flavours; esp. any of numerous cultivated kinds produced throughout the temperate zones of both hemispheres, typically having crisp white flesh and green, yellow, or red skin. &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Sense #12 &lt;BR&gt;rotten (also bad) apple: a negative or corrupting influence on others; a troublesome or despicable person; cf. phrases 2. &lt;BR&gt;First use: George H. Devol &lt;BR&gt;Part of speech: NN &lt;BR&gt;1887 -  &lt;BR&gt;</Answer>
      <SuperMemoReference>&amp;lt;H5 dir=ltr align=left&amp;gt;&amp;lt;Font size=&amp;quot;1&amp;quot; style=&amp;quot;color: transparent&amp;quot;&amp;gt; SuperMemo Reference:&amp;lt;/font&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;&amp;lt;FONT class=reference&amp;gt;Title:&amp;quot;My Test Quote&amp;quot; &amp;lt;br&amp;gt;Source: Oxford English Dictionary</SuperMemoReference>
    </Content>
  </SuperMemoElement>
  <SuperMemoElement>
    <ID>13</ID>
    <Title>apple_nn01-13</Title>
    <Type>Item</Type>
    <Content>
      <Question>Quotation #1I saw the apple in his throat rise and fall with the effort he made to swallow.&lt;BR&gt;S. J. Weyman, From Mem. Minister of France &lt;BR&gt;1895 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #2He looked..up and down the quay, a big apple bulging in his neck.&lt;BR&gt;J. Joyce, Ulysses &lt;BR&gt;1922 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #3I love all the world And the movement of the apple in your throat.&lt;BR&gt;C. Fry, Phoenix too Frequent &lt;BR&gt;1946 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #4Put one hand on the apple of the hound's throat and the other at the back of his head.&lt;BR&gt;, N.Y. Times Bk. Rev. &lt;BR&gt;1992 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;</Question>
      <Answer>The round firm fruit (a pome) of any of various wild and cultivated trees of the genus Malus (see sense 4a), occurring in a wide variety of forms, colours, and flavours; esp. any of numerous cultivated kinds produced throughout the temperate zones of both hemispheres, typically having crisp white flesh and green, yellow, or red skin. &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Sense #13 &lt;BR&gt;= Adam's apple n. 3. &lt;BR&gt;First use: Stanley Weyman &lt;BR&gt;Part of speech: NN &lt;BR&gt;1895 -  &lt;BR&gt;</Answer>
      <SuperMemoReference>&amp;lt;H5 dir=ltr align=left&amp;gt;&amp;lt;Font size=&amp;quot;1&amp;quot; style=&amp;quot;color: transparent&amp;quot;&amp;gt; SuperMemo Reference:&amp;lt;/font&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;&amp;lt;FONT class=reference&amp;gt;Title:&amp;quot;My Test Quote&amp;quot; &amp;lt;br&amp;gt;Source: Oxford English Dictionary</SuperMemoReference>
    </Content>
  </SuperMemoElement>
  <SuperMemoElement>
    <ID>14</ID>
    <Title>apple_nn01-14</Title>
    <Type>Item</Type>
    <Content>
      <Question>Quotation #1A gang of apple knockers strolled toward Mendon.., with Charles Dewey, the famous twirler.&lt;BR&gt;, Delphos (Ohio) Daily Herald &lt;BR&gt;1902 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #2Bert is playing a great game at third base and riding the old apple with wonderful severity.&lt;BR&gt;, Lincoln (Nebraska) Daily News &lt;BR&gt;1914 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #3Jo-jo belts the old apple right through a high window.&lt;BR&gt;D. Runyon, Collier's &lt;BR&gt;1931 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #4Just when I raised my arms to throw to second, the damn apple slipped out of my hand.&lt;BR&gt;R. A. Spears, NTC's Dict. Amer. Slang &lt;BR&gt;1989 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #5I'm glad Marbury is a Knick, but he sure does like to chuck that old apple, doesn't he?&lt;BR&gt;, Daily News (N.Y.) &lt;BR&gt;2004 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;</Question>
      <Answer>The round firm fruit (a pome) of any of various wild and cultivated trees of the genus Malus (see sense 4a), occurring in a wide variety of forms, colours, and flavours; esp. any of numerous cultivated kinds produced throughout the temperate zones of both hemispheres, typically having crisp white flesh and green, yellow, or red skin. &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Sense #14 &lt;BR&gt;U.S. colloquial. A baseball. Also more fully old apple. &lt;BR&gt;First use: Delphos (Ohio) Daily Herald &lt;BR&gt;Part of speech: NN &lt;BR&gt;1902 -  &lt;BR&gt;</Answer>
      <SuperMemoReference>&amp;lt;H5 dir=ltr align=left&amp;gt;&amp;lt;Font size=&amp;quot;1&amp;quot; style=&amp;quot;color: transparent&amp;quot;&amp;gt; SuperMemo Reference:&amp;lt;/font&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;&amp;lt;FONT class=reference&amp;gt;Title:&amp;quot;My Test Quote&amp;quot; &amp;lt;br&amp;gt;Source: Oxford English Dictionary</SuperMemoReference>
    </Content>
  </SuperMemoElement>
  <SuperMemoElement>
    <ID>15</ID>
    <Title>apple_nn01-15</Title>
    <Type>Item</Type>
    <Content>
      <Question>Quotation #1Colours: Peach, Apple, Apricot, Mauve, Fuchsia, Periwinkle.&lt;BR&gt;, Daily Mail &lt;BR&gt;1923 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #2Mini dress..coffee, apple, rose or delphinium print on green.&lt;BR&gt;, Guardian &lt;BR&gt;1970 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #3Five minutes later, the same outfit again—this time in tangerine, then apple, then citrus.&lt;BR&gt;, Independent &lt;BR&gt;1995 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #4The hottest summer colours..include the dusted pastels of violet, poppy, apple,.&lt;BR&gt;, Glebe &amp; Inner City News (Austral.) &lt;BR&gt;2000 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;</Question>
      <Answer>The round firm fruit (a pome) of any of various wild and cultivated trees of the genus Malus (see sense 4a), occurring in a wide variety of forms, colours, and flavours; esp. any of numerous cultivated kinds produced throughout the temperate zones of both hemispheres, typically having crisp white flesh and green, yellow, or red skin. &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Sense #15 &lt;BR&gt;A shade of green resembling the colour of a green apple. Cf. apple green n. adj. at  compounds 2. &lt;BR&gt;First use: Daily Mail &lt;BR&gt;Part of speech: NN &lt;BR&gt;1923 -  &lt;BR&gt;</Answer>
      <SuperMemoReference>&amp;lt;H5 dir=ltr align=left&amp;gt;&amp;lt;Font size=&amp;quot;1&amp;quot; style=&amp;quot;color: transparent&amp;quot;&amp;gt; SuperMemo Reference:&amp;lt;/font&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;&amp;lt;FONT class=reference&amp;gt;Title:&amp;quot;My Test Quote&amp;quot; &amp;lt;br&amp;gt;Source: Oxford English Dictionary</SuperMemoReference>
    </Content>
  </SuperMemoElement>
  <SuperMemoElement>
    <ID>16</ID>
    <Title>apple_nn01-16</Title>
    <Type>Item</Type>
    <Content>
      <Question>Quotation #1No. 1711 has the smart ‘apple bowl’. A sporty looker, and a mighty friendly, comfortable pipe.&lt;BR&gt;, Life &lt;BR&gt;1926 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #2The ‘Apple’ and the ‘Prince’ are examples of smaller, lighter bowls.&lt;BR&gt;A. Dunhill, Gentle Art of Smoking &lt;BR&gt;1954 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #3He lit a pipe, his largest shell-briar Apple.&lt;BR&gt;M. J. Bosse, Incident at Naha &lt;BR&gt;1972 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #4Hand-carved pipes..including..a roughneck with an apple bowl for $18.95.&lt;BR&gt;, Daily Oklahoman (Okla. City, Okla.) &lt;BR&gt;1994 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #5Apple, a classic pipe bowl shape resembling the roundness of an apple.&lt;BR&gt;D. Wright, Pipe Compan. &lt;BR&gt;2000 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;</Question>
      <Answer>The round firm fruit (a pome) of any of various wild and cultivated trees of the genus Malus (see sense 4a), occurring in a wide variety of forms, colours, and flavours; esp. any of numerous cultivated kinds produced throughout the temperate zones of both hemispheres, typically having crisp white flesh and green, yellow, or red skin. &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Sense #16 &lt;BR&gt;Also with capital initial. A round, apple-shaped bowl on a tobacco pipe (also more fully apple bowl); a tobacco pipe with such a bowl. &lt;BR&gt;First use: Life &lt;BR&gt;Part of speech: NN &lt;BR&gt;1926 -  &lt;BR&gt;</Answer>
      <SuperMemoReference>&amp;lt;H5 dir=ltr align=left&amp;gt;&amp;lt;Font size=&amp;quot;1&amp;quot; style=&amp;quot;color: transparent&amp;quot;&amp;gt; SuperMemo Reference:&amp;lt;/font&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;&amp;lt;FONT class=reference&amp;gt;Title:&amp;quot;My Test Quote&amp;quot; &amp;lt;br&amp;gt;Source: Oxford English Dictionary</SuperMemoReference>
    </Content>
  </SuperMemoElement>
  <SuperMemoElement>
    <ID>17</ID>
    <Title>apple_nn01-17</Title>
    <Type>Item</Type>
    <Content>
      <Question>Quotation #1‘I can't say,’ replied the poor apple.&lt;BR&gt;S. J. Perelman, Judge &lt;BR&gt;1928 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #2Boys do not meet with subdeb approval..are lumped together under such terms as..sad apples, meatballs,..and drips.&lt;BR&gt;, Life Mag. &lt;BR&gt;1941 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #3That's a different department; I don't hobnob with those apples.&lt;BR&gt;R. P. Davis, Pilot &lt;BR&gt;1976 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #4Leonard himself was a pretty tough apple.&lt;BR&gt;, Business Week &lt;BR&gt;2004 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;</Question>
      <Answer>The round firm fruit (a pome) of any of various wild and cultivated trees of the genus Malus (see sense 4a), occurring in a wide variety of forms, colours, and flavours; esp. any of numerous cultivated kinds produced throughout the temperate zones of both hemispheres, typically having crisp white flesh and green, yellow, or red skin. &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Sense #17 &lt;BR&gt;colloquial (chiefly U.S.). A person; a fellow, a guy. Usually with preceding adjective. &lt;BR&gt;First use: S. J. Perelman &lt;BR&gt;Part of speech: NN &lt;BR&gt;1928 -  &lt;BR&gt;</Answer>
      <SuperMemoReference>&amp;lt;H5 dir=ltr align=left&amp;gt;&amp;lt;Font size=&amp;quot;1&amp;quot; style=&amp;quot;color: transparent&amp;quot;&amp;gt; SuperMemo Reference:&amp;lt;/font&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;&amp;lt;FONT class=reference&amp;gt;Title:&amp;quot;My Test Quote&amp;quot; &amp;lt;br&amp;gt;Source: Oxford English Dictionary</SuperMemoReference>
    </Content>
  </SuperMemoElement>
  <SuperMemoElement>
    <ID>18</ID>
    <Title>apple_nn01-18</Title>
    <Type>Item</Type>
    <Content>
      <Question>Quotation #1Apple, the big town, the main stem, Harlem.&lt;BR&gt;C. Calloway, New Cab Calloway's Cat-ologue &lt;BR&gt;1939 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #2I'll write you from the apple.&lt;BR&gt;R. Ellison, Let. &lt;BR&gt;1953 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #3Both groups are symptomatic of the flood of young musicians storming into the Apple, abandoning studio sinecures and rock bands to play difficult improvisatory music.&lt;BR&gt;G. Giddins, Village Voice (N.Y.) &lt;BR&gt;1974 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #4Many of the city's most creative people in the 1970s (as now) were high IQ boys and girls from Smalltown who fled to the Apple.&lt;BR&gt;, Wall St. Jrnl. &lt;BR&gt;2005 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;</Question>
      <Answer>The round firm fruit (a pome) of any of various wild and cultivated trees of the genus Malus (see sense 4a), occurring in a wide variety of forms, colours, and flavours; esp. any of numerous cultivated kinds produced throughout the temperate zones of both hemispheres, typically having crisp white flesh and green, yellow, or red skin. &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Sense #18 &lt;BR&gt;U.S. slang (originally Jazz). Usually with capital initial. With the. Originally: Harlem. Hence later: New York City. Cf. Big Apple n. 4. &lt;BR&gt;First use: Cab Calloway &lt;BR&gt;Part of speech: NN &lt;BR&gt;1939 -  &lt;BR&gt;</Answer>
      <SuperMemoReference>&amp;lt;H5 dir=ltr align=left&amp;gt;&amp;lt;Font size=&amp;quot;1&amp;quot; style=&amp;quot;color: transparent&amp;quot;&amp;gt; SuperMemo Reference:&amp;lt;/font&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;&amp;lt;FONT class=reference&amp;gt;Title:&amp;quot;My Test Quote&amp;quot; &amp;lt;br&amp;gt;Source: Oxford English Dictionary</SuperMemoReference>
    </Content>
  </SuperMemoElement>
  <SuperMemoElement>
    <ID>19</ID>
    <Title>apple_nn01-19</Title>
    <Type>Item</Type>
    <Content>
      <Question>Quotation #1If everything is running smoothly ‘she's apples’.&lt;BR&gt;J. Binning, Target Area &lt;BR&gt;1943 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #2How's it going, Wally? Everything apples?&lt;BR&gt;T. A. G. Hungerford, Ridge &amp; River &lt;BR&gt;1952 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #3She felt their faint movements of relief and surprise. ‘Well,’ said Dixon, ‘that'd be a break. That'd be apples, that would.’&lt;BR&gt;R. Stow, To Islands &lt;BR&gt;1958 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #4Don't cry, Pru. Yuh go and see old Len Ramsbottom and betcha everything'll be apples.&lt;BR&gt;R. H. Morrieson, Scarecrow &lt;BR&gt;1963 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #5No one reckons it's ‘apples’ in the battle for Bass.&lt;BR&gt;, Sydney Morning Herald &lt;BR&gt;1975 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #6She's apples. Now you just lie back an' take it easy.&lt;BR&gt;R. Beilby, Gunner &lt;BR&gt;1977 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #7Apples &amp; Rice, nice. Generally shortened to the first element when describing something that is nice, e.g. ‘She's apples’. But used in full when used to describe something that isn't, e.g., ‘Oh, that's very apples and rice. I'm out of work and you're pregnant again.’&lt;BR&gt;R. Puxley, Cockney Rabbit &lt;BR&gt;1992 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #8Well, she's not much of a motor, but with a spray job and a new radiator she'll be apples!&lt;BR&gt;, Fast Forward &lt;BR&gt;1994 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;</Question>
      <Answer>The round firm fruit (a pome) of any of various wild and cultivated trees of the genus Malus (see sense 4a), occurring in a wide variety of forms, colours, and flavours; esp. any of numerous cultivated kinds produced throughout the temperate zones of both hemispheres, typically having crisp white flesh and green, yellow, or red skin. &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Sense #19 &lt;BR&gt;slang (chiefly Australian and New Zealand). Used to indicate a state of affairs regarded as good or satisfactory (or occasionally ironic the reverse). Chiefly in she's (also it's) apples and variants: everything is all right; things will be fine (see she pron.1 2a(e)). &lt;BR&gt;First use: J. Binning &lt;BR&gt;Part of speech: NN &lt;BR&gt;1943 -  &lt;BR&gt;</Answer>
      <SuperMemoReference>&amp;lt;H5 dir=ltr align=left&amp;gt;&amp;lt;Font size=&amp;quot;1&amp;quot; style=&amp;quot;color: transparent&amp;quot;&amp;gt; SuperMemo Reference:&amp;lt;/font&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;&amp;lt;FONT class=reference&amp;gt;Title:&amp;quot;My Test Quote&amp;quot; &amp;lt;br&amp;gt;Source: Oxford English Dictionary</SuperMemoReference>
    </Content>
  </SuperMemoElement>
  <SuperMemoElement>
    <ID>20</ID>
    <Title>apple_nn01-20</Title>
    <Type>Item</Type>
    <Content>
      <Question>Quotation #1Her 8-year-old boy criticized her 10-year-old daughter by calling her an ‘apple.’&lt;BR&gt;, Lawton (Okla.) Constit. &lt;BR&gt;1970 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #2The ‘apples’, who categorically reject the Indian culture they were born to, choose one side, the white.&lt;BR&gt;P. G. Allen, Sacred Hoop &lt;BR&gt;1986 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #3You ain't shit, you fucking apple.&lt;BR&gt;R. Hendrickson, Happy Trails &lt;BR&gt;1994 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #4I never saw money to do good things to Indians, it turns them into ‘Apples’—red on the outside, white in the middle.&lt;BR&gt;, Adrenalin &lt;BR&gt;2001 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;</Question>
      <Answer>The round firm fruit (a pome) of any of various wild and cultivated trees of the genus Malus (see sense 4a), occurring in a wide variety of forms, colours, and flavours; esp. any of numerous cultivated kinds produced throughout the temperate zones of both hemispheres, typically having crisp white flesh and green, yellow, or red skin. &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Sense #20 &lt;BR&gt;U.S. slang (derogatory). In North American Indian usage: a North American Indian regarded as espousing or adopting the values of white society or culture (see quot. 2001). Cf. Oreo n.1 2. &lt;BR&gt;First use: Lawton (Okla.) Constit. &lt;BR&gt;Part of speech: NN &lt;BR&gt;1970 -  &lt;BR&gt;</Answer>
      <SuperMemoReference>&amp;lt;H5 dir=ltr align=left&amp;gt;&amp;lt;Font size=&amp;quot;1&amp;quot; style=&amp;quot;color: transparent&amp;quot;&amp;gt; SuperMemo Reference:&amp;lt;/font&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;&amp;lt;FONT class=reference&amp;gt;Title:&amp;quot;My Test Quote&amp;quot; &amp;lt;br&amp;gt;Source: Oxford English Dictionary</SuperMemoReference>
    </Content>
  </SuperMemoElement>
  <SuperMemoElement>
    <ID>21</ID>
    <Title>apple_vb01-1</Title>
    <Type>Item</Type>
    <Content>
      <Question>Quotation #1For all the sort of them during the Summer throughout, never rest and give over, but either they floure, or they apple, or els be readie to bring foorth fruit.&lt;BR&gt;P. Holland, Hist. World &lt;BR&gt;1601 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #2To Pome or Apple, is said of the Heads of Artichokes when they grow round, and full shaped as an Apple. It is said also of Lettuce, &amp;c.&lt;BR&gt;J. Evelyn, Compl. Gard'ner &lt;BR&gt;1693 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #3Unless the Soil has some mixture of Sand the Turnips do not apple, as they call it: that is, do not bottom well.&lt;BR&gt;J. Morton, Nat. Hist. Northants. &lt;BR&gt;1712 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #4The Turneps grew 'till Christmas or longer, and appled well in gravelly or stony Grounds, because their Roots can't here enter so deep.&lt;BR&gt;W. Ellis, Mod. Husbandman &lt;BR&gt;1750 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #5The cabbage turnep is of two kinds; one apples above ground, and the other in it.&lt;BR&gt;C. Marshall, Introd. Knowl. &amp; Pract. Gardening &lt;BR&gt;1798 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #6Apple, to bottom at the roots. Turnips apple well, when the roots well, and assume a bulbous form.&lt;BR&gt;A. E. Baker, Gloss. Northants. Words &lt;BR&gt;1854 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #7The fine-leaved turnips that have escaped the fly, but have still to ‘apple’.&lt;BR&gt;P. H. Emerson, Birds, Beasts, &amp; Fishes Norfolk Broadland &lt;BR&gt;1895 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #8Potatoes and onions are said to apple when they develop properly. A dialect use.&lt;BR&gt;E. Gepp, Essex Dial. Dict. &lt;BR&gt;1923 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #9Me taters be n't applin' like they ed ough'ter.&lt;BR&gt;M. Carbery, Herts. Heritage &lt;BR&gt;1948 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #10Them blubs (bulbs) what we put awaay int' spring's gone an' appled nicely.&lt;BR&gt;J. M. Sims-Kimbrey, Wodds &amp; Doggerybaw: Lincs. Dial. Dict. &lt;BR&gt;1995 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;</Question>
      <Answer>intransitive. Of vegetables, flower buds, and esp. (in later use) root crops: to swell into a globular shape; to become shaped like an apple. &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Sense #1 &lt;BR&gt;intransitive. Of vegetables, flower buds, and esp. (in later use) root crops: to swell into a globular shape; to become shaped like an apple. &lt;BR&gt;First use: Philemon Holland &lt;BR&gt;Part of speech: VB &lt;BR&gt;1601 -  &lt;BR&gt;This is the main current sense &lt;BR&gt;</Answer>
      <SuperMemoReference>&amp;lt;H5 dir=ltr align=left&amp;gt;&amp;lt;Font size=&amp;quot;1&amp;quot; style=&amp;quot;color: transparent&amp;quot;&amp;gt; SuperMemo Reference:&amp;lt;/font&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;&amp;lt;FONT class=reference&amp;gt;Title:&amp;quot;My Test Quote&amp;quot; &amp;lt;br&amp;gt;Source: Oxford English Dictionary</SuperMemoReference>
    </Content>
  </SuperMemoElement>
  <SuperMemoElement>
    <ID>22</ID>
    <Title>apple_vb01-2</Title>
    <Type>Item</Type>
    <Content>
      <Question>Quotation #1The poor people supply themselves with very good fuel by gathering the fir-apples and rotten wood; you will sometimes see twenty children in my plantations appleing, as they call it.&lt;BR&gt;A. Young, Gen. View Agric. County Lincoln &lt;BR&gt;1799 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #2Going out appling is going out into the woods to collect fir cones for burning.&lt;BR&gt;J. M. Sims-Kimbrey, Wodds &amp; Doggerybaw: Lincs. Dial. Dict. &lt;BR&gt;1995 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;</Question>
      <Answer>intransitive. Of vegetables, flower buds, and esp. (in later use) root crops: to swell into a globular shape; to become shaped like an apple. &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Sense #2 &lt;BR&gt;intransitive. To gather fir cones (see fir-apple n. at  fir n. compounds 2). rare. &lt;BR&gt;First use: Arthur Young &lt;BR&gt;Part of speech: VB &lt;BR&gt;1799 -  &lt;BR&gt;</Answer>
      <SuperMemoReference>&amp;lt;H5 dir=ltr align=left&amp;gt;&amp;lt;Font size=&amp;quot;1&amp;quot; style=&amp;quot;color: transparent&amp;quot;&amp;gt; SuperMemo Reference:&amp;lt;/font&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;&amp;lt;FONT class=reference&amp;gt;Title:&amp;quot;My Test Quote&amp;quot; &amp;lt;br&amp;gt;Source: Oxford English Dictionary</SuperMemoReference>
    </Content>
  </SuperMemoElement>
  <SuperMemoElement>
    <ID>23</ID>
    <Title>apple_nn01-1</Title>
    <Type>Item</Type>
    <Content>
      <Question>Quotation #1On ðaes siwenigean eagum beoð ða aepplas hale, ac ða braewas greatigað,..oððaet sio scearpnes bið gewird ðaes aepples.&lt;BR&gt;King Aelfred, Pastoral Care &lt;BR&gt;895 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #2Ðurh ðone aepl ðaes eagan mon maeg geseon.&lt;BR&gt;King Aelfred, Pastoral Care &lt;BR&gt;895 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #3La prunele, the appel of the eye.&lt;BR&gt;W. de Biblesworth,  &lt;BR&gt;1299 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #4The Appyll of ye ee, pupilla.&lt;BR&gt;, Catholicon Anglicum &lt;BR&gt;1475 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #5We see our owne eies shine within the apples of our neighbours eies.&lt;BR&gt;T. Bowes, French Acad. &lt;BR&gt;1586 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #6The dart did undergore His eye-lid, by his eye's dear roots, &amp; out the apple fell.&lt;BR&gt;G. Chapman, Iliad &lt;BR&gt;1600 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #7None have their eyes all of one color, for the bal or apple in the midst is ordinarily of another color than the white about.&lt;BR&gt;P. Holland, Hist. World &lt;BR&gt;1601 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #8Having carefully observ'd the Eyes of several Fishes..I found that the..Pupil or Apple of the Eye, was very flat, like those in Human Creatures.&lt;BR&gt;, Philos. Trans. 1704–05 &lt;BR&gt;1705 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #9He cut asunder the Apple of the eye in several animals.&lt;BR&gt;, Chambers's Cycl. &lt;BR&gt;1753 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #10Dull people turn up..the apples of their eyes on beholding Prose by a Poet.&lt;BR&gt;, Blackwood's Edinb. Mag. &lt;BR&gt;1827 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #11Large dark blue sparkling eye..with much white, of a bluish shade, visible under the apple.&lt;BR&gt;, Anthropol. Rev. &lt;BR&gt;1870 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #12The eye was also considered so as to elucidate the origin and application of such terms as bulb, apple, iris, pupil, cataract.&lt;BR&gt;, Lancet &lt;BR&gt;1912 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #13Just you take a look at Jimmy here's eye..two circles there be, one for range and t'other for intelligence, and locked up in the apple, sir.&lt;BR&gt;H. Williamson, Golden Virgin &lt;BR&gt;1957 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #14At this time the pupil of the eye was thought to be a solid object and was known as the apple because it was spherical.&lt;BR&gt;, People &lt;BR&gt;2004 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;</Question>
      <Answer>The round firm fruit (a pome) of any of various wild and cultivated trees of the genus Malus (see sense 4a), occurring in a wide variety of forms, colours, and flavours; esp. any of numerous cultivated kinds produced throughout the temperate zones of both hemispheres, typically having crisp white flesh and green, yellow, or red skin. &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Sense #1 &lt;BR&gt;More fully apple of the eye. The pupil of the eye, originally thought to be a solid, spherical body. Occasionally also: the iris and pupil, or the whole eyeball. Now historical. &lt;BR&gt;First use: King Alfred &lt;BR&gt;Part of speech: NN &lt;BR&gt;895 -  &lt;BR&gt;</Answer>
      <SuperMemoReference>&amp;lt;H5 dir=ltr align=left&amp;gt;&amp;lt;Font size=&amp;quot;1&amp;quot; style=&amp;quot;color: transparent&amp;quot;&amp;gt; SuperMemo Reference:&amp;lt;/font&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;&amp;lt;FONT class=reference&amp;gt;Title:&amp;quot;My Test Quote&amp;quot; &amp;lt;br&amp;gt;Source: Oxford English Dictionary</SuperMemoReference>
    </Content>
  </SuperMemoElement>
  <SuperMemoElement>
    <ID>24</ID>
    <Title>apple_nn01-2</Title>
    <Type>Item</Type>
    <Content>
      <Question>Quotation #1Spere, aepples.&lt;BR&gt;, Cleopatra Gloss. &lt;BR&gt;935 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #2Worpað hine deofol on domdaege, draca egeslice, bismorlice, of blacere liðran irenum aplum.&lt;BR&gt;, Metrical Dialogue of Solomon &amp; Saturn &lt;BR&gt;1045 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #3He was wont to holden a round appell of gold in his hond.&lt;BR&gt;, Mandeville's Trav. &lt;BR&gt;1424 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #4Ȝe most forsake of golde ȝowre appil rounde Sceptre and swerde.&lt;BR&gt;J. Lydgate, Daunce Machabree &lt;BR&gt;1430 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #5To make ye apple of the chieck ruddy.&lt;BR&gt;P. Morwyng, Treasure of Euonymus &lt;BR&gt;1559 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #6The knight kneeleth..with his naked sworde vnder his arme, the whiche beeing made of Iasper sprinkled with Uermilion spots, seemeth to be al bloudy, &amp; hee presenteth an apple of the same stone to the Princesse.&lt;BR&gt;H. Wotton, Courtlie Controuersie &lt;BR&gt;1578 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #7Hold a round ball or hollow apple of glasse.&lt;BR&gt;P. Holland, Hist. World &lt;BR&gt;1601 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #8You that carried Summer in your lips..That in the Apples of your cheeks did wear A fertile Autumn now no fruit can bear?&lt;BR&gt;R. Heath, Clarastella &lt;BR&gt;1650 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #9Shrugging up her Shoulders, to shew the tempting Apples of her white Breasts.&lt;BR&gt;J. S., City &amp; Country Recreation &lt;BR&gt;1705 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #10The Vane on the Top of the Steeple is a Piece of fine Work..at the Extremity is a large gilded Apple or Globe.&lt;BR&gt;W. Guthrie, Trav. &lt;BR&gt;1743 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #11A Venus, with the Wand or Hasta pura in one Hand, and the Golden Apple or Globe in the other.&lt;BR&gt;W. Cooke, Medallic Hist. Imperial Rome &lt;BR&gt;1781 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #12He press'd His hand upon the apples of my breast.&lt;BR&gt;‘Philocomus’, Love Feast &lt;BR&gt;1865 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #13Of double-faced Canton flannel, finished with fringe and floss apples.&lt;BR&gt;, N.Y. Art Interchange &lt;BR&gt;1881 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #14Andy picked up his two grenades... The apples felt strangely heavy in his hands.&lt;BR&gt;M. Hargrove, Girl he left Behind &lt;BR&gt;1956 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #15Thereafter the ‘imperial apple’ became an important emblem of the royal power invested in the monarch.&lt;BR&gt;, Encycl. Brit. Macropaedia &lt;BR&gt;1974 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #16A peasant blouse that showed the top of those lovely little apples.&lt;BR&gt;C. W. Smith, Country Music &lt;BR&gt;1975 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #17Apply powder blush directly to the apple of the cheek.&lt;BR&gt;, Red &lt;BR&gt;2004 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;</Question>
      <Answer>The round firm fruit (a pome) of any of various wild and cultivated trees of the genus Malus (see sense 4a), occurring in a wide variety of forms, colours, and flavours; esp. any of numerous cultivated kinds produced throughout the temperate zones of both hemispheres, typically having crisp white flesh and green, yellow, or red skin. &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Sense #2 &lt;BR&gt;Any of various things resembling an apple in form or colour; spec. = pome n.1 2. &lt;BR&gt;First use: Cleopatra Glossary &lt;BR&gt;Part of speech: NN &lt;BR&gt;935 -  &lt;BR&gt;</Answer>
      <SuperMemoReference>&amp;lt;H5 dir=ltr align=left&amp;gt;&amp;lt;Font size=&amp;quot;1&amp;quot; style=&amp;quot;color: transparent&amp;quot;&amp;gt; SuperMemo Reference:&amp;lt;/font&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;&amp;lt;FONT class=reference&amp;gt;Title:&amp;quot;My Test Quote&amp;quot; &amp;lt;br&amp;gt;Source: Oxford English Dictionary</SuperMemoReference>
    </Content>
  </SuperMemoElement>
  <SuperMemoElement>
    <ID>25</ID>
    <Title>apple_nn01-3</Title>
    <Type>Item</Type>
    <Content>
      <Question>Quotation #1Mala punica, ða affricaniscan aeppla.&lt;BR&gt;, Cleopatra Gloss. &lt;BR&gt;935 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #2Genim brembelaeppel &amp; elehtran &amp; pollegian, gecnua.&lt;BR&gt;, Bald's Leechbk. &lt;BR&gt;950 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #3We haefdon cucumeres, þaet sind eorðaepla, &amp; pepones &amp; porleac &amp; enneleac &amp; manega oþre þingc.&lt;BR&gt;, Old Eng. Hexateuch: Num. &lt;BR&gt;1025 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #4Þe Applene weren ripe inouȝ, riȝt ase it heruest were.&lt;BR&gt;, St. Brendan &lt;BR&gt;1300 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #5Quane here apples ripe ben, fier-isles man mai ðor-inne sen.&lt;BR&gt;, Gen. &amp; Exod. &lt;BR&gt;1324 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #6Alle maner appul þat is closed in an harde skyn, rynde or schale is ycleped nux.&lt;BR&gt;J. Trevisa, De Proprietatibus Rerum &lt;BR&gt;1397 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #7Þar-bi groues sum apell tre, Wit appuls selcut fair to se, Quen þai ar in hand, als a fise bal, To poudir wit a stink þai fal.&lt;BR&gt;, Cursor Mundi &lt;BR&gt;1399 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #8Take þe appullis of sypressus and ete hem or þe pouder of þe applys dryed.&lt;BR&gt;, Practica Phisicalia John of Burgundy &lt;BR&gt;1450 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #9Venemous apples wherwith they poyson theyr arrowes.&lt;BR&gt;R. Eden, Decades of Newe Worlde &lt;BR&gt;1555 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #10The Mandrake..beareth sayth Isidore, an Apple of sweete smell, which of some is called the Apple of the earth.&lt;BR&gt;J. Maplet, Greene Forest &lt;BR&gt;1567 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #11Hereof commeth the colour Puniceus (i. a light red or a bay) taking the name of the apple Punicke or Pomegranate.&lt;BR&gt;P. Holland, Hist. World &lt;BR&gt;1601 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #12The fruite or Apples of Palme-trees.&lt;BR&gt;E. Topsell, Hist. Foure-footed Beastes &lt;BR&gt;1607 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #13The other trees gave no fruit; an uselesse apple from the Oak, or little berries from the Laurel and the Myrtle.&lt;BR&gt;Bp. J. Taylor, Worthy Communicant &lt;BR&gt;1660 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #14The apples call'd pompions by the Dutch,..grow scarce anywhere else in the Indies but in the Isle of Great Java.&lt;BR&gt;, Voy. E.-Indies &lt;BR&gt;1704 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #15It is remarkable for producing great quantities of that delicious fruit we called apples.&lt;BR&gt;J. Cook, Voy. Pacific &lt;BR&gt;1784 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #16The Custard-apples, Sweetsops, and Soursops, of the East and West Indies, are furnished by various species of Anona.&lt;BR&gt;J. H. Balfour, Man. Bot. &lt;BR&gt;1849 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #17Then came a course of fruits grown upon the place: luscious ‘Ripley’ Pine Apples and Star Apples (the latter..when cut across, displayed the seed chambers arranged in the exact form of a star).&lt;BR&gt;, Harper's Mag. &lt;BR&gt;1858 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #18It is a much-branched small tree or shrub, reaching a height of 6 meters, and is also known as the Punic apple.&lt;BR&gt;N. L. Britton, N. Amer. Trees &lt;BR&gt;1908 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #19A section of the ‘potato apple’ is like that of the tomato.&lt;BR&gt;, Times Educ. Suppl. &lt;BR&gt;1930 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #20I had inadvertently cut the branch of an overhanging manzanillo tree, whose apples are poison to humans.&lt;BR&gt;, Smithsonian &lt;BR&gt;2005 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;</Question>
      <Answer>The round firm fruit (a pome) of any of various wild and cultivated trees of the genus Malus (see sense 4a), occurring in a wide variety of forms, colours, and flavours; esp. any of numerous cultivated kinds produced throughout the temperate zones of both hemispheres, typically having crisp white flesh and green, yellow, or red skin. &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Sense #3 &lt;BR&gt;Frequently with distinguishing word: any of various fruits (and vegetables), esp. those thought to resemble the apple (sense 1) in some way; any of the plants producing such a fruit (or vegetable). &lt;BR&gt;First use: Cleopatra Glossary &lt;BR&gt;Part of speech: NN &lt;BR&gt;935 -  &lt;BR&gt;</Answer>
      <SuperMemoReference>&amp;lt;H5 dir=ltr align=left&amp;gt;&amp;lt;Font size=&amp;quot;1&amp;quot; style=&amp;quot;color: transparent&amp;quot;&amp;gt; SuperMemo Reference:&amp;lt;/font&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;&amp;lt;FONT class=reference&amp;gt;Title:&amp;quot;My Test Quote&amp;quot; &amp;lt;br&amp;gt;Source: Oxford English Dictionary</SuperMemoReference>
    </Content>
  </SuperMemoElement>
  <SuperMemoElement>
    <ID>26</ID>
    <Title>apple_nn01-4</Title>
    <Type>Item</Type>
    <Content>
      <Question>Quotation #1Se godcunda anwald gefrioðode his deorlingas under fiðra sceate, &amp; hi scilde swa geornlice swa man deð þone aeppel on his eagan.&lt;BR&gt;King Aelfred, De Consol. Philos. &lt;BR&gt;950 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #2Geheald me, Drihten, and beorh me, swa swa man byrhð þam aeplum on his eagum mid his braewum.&lt;BR&gt;King Aelfred, Psalms &lt;BR&gt;1050 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #3Kepe me..as þe appel of þyn eȝe.&lt;BR&gt;, Psalter &lt;BR&gt;1350 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #4Als appel ofe eghe yheme þou me.&lt;BR&gt;, Psalter &lt;BR&gt;1399 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #5If you touche him in the Indies, you touche the apple of his eye.&lt;BR&gt;R. Hakluyt, Disc. Western Planting &lt;BR&gt;1584 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #6that shall nourish no blood but your owne, tender your reputation as the apple of her eye, &amp; honour euen your verie footsteps.&lt;BR&gt;E. Sharpham, Cupids Whirligig &lt;BR&gt;1607 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #7He can't live without you. You're the Apple of his Eye, the Joy of his Heart, the Lamp of his Life.&lt;BR&gt;J. Bancroft, Henry II &lt;BR&gt;1693 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #8His daughter beautiful and young..The perfect picture of her mother's youth, His age's hope, the apple of his eye.&lt;BR&gt;M. Bruce, Poems &lt;BR&gt;1766 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #9Poor Richard was to me as an eldest son, the apple of my eye.&lt;BR&gt;W. Scott, Old Mortality &lt;BR&gt;1816 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #10Col. Gildersleeve has lost his valuable setter dog Don, which animal was the apple of his eye.&lt;BR&gt;, Spirit of Times &lt;BR&gt;1877 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #11He was a master of his profession, and his journal was to him as the apple of his eye.&lt;BR&gt;, Harper's Mag. &lt;BR&gt;1884 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #12Live and die The apple, nay the onion, of his eye?&lt;BR&gt;R. Campbell, Poems &lt;BR&gt;1930 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #13He parked his 1932 Mercedes-Benz (he called it the apple of his eye) outside A Block.&lt;BR&gt;R. Mistry, Tales from Firozsha Baag &lt;BR&gt;1987 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #14Errol was the apple of my grandmother's eye because he was her eldest.&lt;BR&gt;P. Jooste, Dance with Poor Man's Daughter &lt;BR&gt;1998 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;</Question>
      <Answer>The round firm fruit (a pome) of any of various wild and cultivated trees of the genus Malus (see sense 4a), occurring in a wide variety of forms, colours, and flavours; esp. any of numerous cultivated kinds produced throughout the temperate zones of both hemispheres, typically having crisp white flesh and green, yellow, or red skin. &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Sense #4 &lt;BR&gt;More fully apple of the eye. figurative and in extended use. Originally: the type of something precious. In later use chiefly the apple of a person's eye: the particular object of a person's affection or regard; a greatly cherished person or occasionally thing. &lt;BR&gt;First use: King Alfred &lt;BR&gt;Part of speech: NN &lt;BR&gt;950 -  &lt;BR&gt;</Answer>
      <SuperMemoReference>&amp;lt;H5 dir=ltr align=left&amp;gt;&amp;lt;Font size=&amp;quot;1&amp;quot; style=&amp;quot;color: transparent&amp;quot;&amp;gt; SuperMemo Reference:&amp;lt;/font&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;&amp;lt;FONT class=reference&amp;gt;Title:&amp;quot;My Test Quote&amp;quot; &amp;lt;br&amp;gt;Source: Oxford English Dictionary</SuperMemoReference>
    </Content>
  </SuperMemoElement>
  <SuperMemoElement>
    <ID>27</ID>
    <Title>apple_nn01-5</Title>
    <Type>Item</Type>
    <Content>
      <Question>Quotation #1Him mon on fruman þa mettas gife..swa swa beoþ aeppla, nales to swete ealles ac surmelsce, &amp; peran &amp; persucas.&lt;BR&gt;, Bald's Leechbk. &lt;BR&gt;950 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #2Wudusuraeppel, fille &amp; finul, ealde sapan. Gewyrc ða wyrta to duste, maengc wiþ þa sapan &amp; wiþ þaes aepples gor.&lt;BR&gt;, Metrical Charm: Nine Herbs &lt;BR&gt;1000 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #3He..bið al swa is an eppel iheoweð.&lt;BR&gt;, MS Lamb. &lt;BR&gt;1224 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #4As he bi huld an hey, Vpe þe hexte bowe tweye applen he sey; &amp; þe bowes of þe on appel smite þe oþer vaste.&lt;BR&gt;, Chron. Robert of Gloucester &lt;BR&gt;1325 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #5I prayed pieres to pulle adown an apple.&lt;BR&gt;W. Langland, Piers Plowman &lt;BR&gt;1400 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #6This tree..bringith forth soure applis.&lt;BR&gt;R. Pecock, Repressor &lt;BR&gt;1449 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #7Rough tasted appules are holsome where the stomake is weake.&lt;BR&gt;T. Elyot, Castel of Helthe &lt;BR&gt;1533 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #8Giue him an Apple, or a Peare, or some such chyldes rewarde.&lt;BR&gt;N. Breton, Floorish vpon Fancie &lt;BR&gt;1577 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #9Syder is usually made of such Apples as are moist sommer fruits.&lt;BR&gt;R. Austen, Treat. Fruit-trees &lt;BR&gt;1653 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #10They commonly mingle water in ye presse wth ye apples (a good quantity) whilst they grind ye apples.&lt;BR&gt;J. Beale, Let. &lt;BR&gt;1663 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #11Venders of..apples, plumbs.&lt;BR&gt;R. Steele, Spectator &lt;BR&gt;1712 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #12Apples arrive to perfection for use..from July or August, until the end of October.&lt;BR&gt;J. Abercrombie, Brit. Fruit-gardener &lt;BR&gt;1779 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #13Most of our best apples are supposed to have been introduced into Britain by a fruiterer of Henry the Eighth.&lt;BR&gt;H. Davy, Elements Agric. Chem. &lt;BR&gt;1813 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #14We count the apple as the King of fruits, because it is more generally known and used than any other.&lt;BR&gt;F. R. Elliot, Hand-bk. for Fruit Growers &lt;BR&gt;1876 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #15With what..delight did we children hover round our elders at night, while they gilded walnuts, or rubbed apples until they were as glossy as our own cheeks.&lt;BR&gt;L. W. Reese, Victorian Village &lt;BR&gt;1929 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #16Many thousands of tons of apples are wasted yearly.&lt;BR&gt;, Times &lt;BR&gt;1952 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #17This handy apple corer/segmenter..will core and slice an apple into 12 even segments easily and simply.&lt;BR&gt;, Weight Watchers Mag. &lt;BR&gt;2006 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;</Question>
      <Answer>The round firm fruit (a pome) of any of various wild and cultivated trees of the genus Malus (see sense 4a), occurring in a wide variety of forms, colours, and flavours; esp. any of numerous cultivated kinds produced throughout the temperate zones of both hemispheres, typically having crisp white flesh and green, yellow, or red skin. &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Sense #5 &lt;BR&gt;The round firm fruit (a pome) of any of various wild and cultivated trees of the genus Malus (see sense 4a), occurring in a wide variety of forms, colours, and flavours; esp. any of numerous cultivated kinds produced throughout the temperate zones of both hemispheres, typically having crisp white flesh and green, yellow, or red skin. &lt;BR&gt;First use: Bald's Leechbook &lt;BR&gt;Part of speech: NN &lt;BR&gt;950 -  &lt;BR&gt;This is the main current sense &lt;BR&gt;</Answer>
      <SuperMemoReference>&amp;lt;H5 dir=ltr align=left&amp;gt;&amp;lt;Font size=&amp;quot;1&amp;quot; style=&amp;quot;color: transparent&amp;quot;&amp;gt; SuperMemo Reference:&amp;lt;/font&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;&amp;lt;FONT class=reference&amp;gt;Title:&amp;quot;My Test Quote&amp;quot; &amp;lt;br&amp;gt;Source: Oxford English Dictionary</SuperMemoReference>
    </Content>
  </SuperMemoElement>
  <SuperMemoElement>
    <ID>28</ID>
    <Title>apple_nn01-6</Title>
    <Type>Item</Type>
    <Content>
      <Question>Quotation #1Aeppel unsaelga, þone hire aer forbead drihtna drihten, deaðbeames ofet.&lt;BR&gt;, Genesis B &lt;BR&gt;1000 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #2Eue bi heold oðe for boden appel.&lt;BR&gt;, Ancrene Riwle &lt;BR&gt;1225 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #3How adam brake goddis comandement of the appil.&lt;BR&gt;, Cursor Mundi &lt;BR&gt;1399 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #4The delite of the apill l slow Eue.&lt;BR&gt;, Bk. Knight of La Tour Landry &lt;BR&gt;1450 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #5Adam, oure alder, þat ete of þat appulle.&lt;BR&gt;, St. Erkenwald &lt;BR&gt;1499 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #6These maner of people sell paradise for an apple, with Adam and Eue.&lt;BR&gt;W. Bonde, Pylgrimage of Perfection &lt;BR&gt;1526 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #7Was it such a sinne for Adam to eate a forbidden Apple? Yes, the greatnes is remonstrable in the euent.&lt;BR&gt;T. Adams, Happines of Church &lt;BR&gt;1618 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #8Him by fraud I have seduc'd From his Creator..with an Apple.&lt;BR&gt;J. Milton, Paradise Lost &lt;BR&gt;1667 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #9To eat Meat that is forbidden, doth defile the Soul, as the Apple defiled Adam's.&lt;BR&gt;J. J. Hornyold, Real Princ. Catholicks &lt;BR&gt;1749 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #10The Apple had done but little for me If Eve had not done the rest.&lt;BR&gt;R. Southey, All for Love &lt;BR&gt;1829 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #11You see, Eva, since Adam took the apple from Eve men have obeyed women nem. con.&lt;BR&gt;H. B. Stowe, My Wife &amp; I &lt;BR&gt;1871 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #12Since man ate the apple..the human emotions are like a wedded wife.&lt;BR&gt;D. H. Lawrence, Phoenix &lt;BR&gt;1924 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #13In the Elizabethan era which, like the Hebraic and Christian, never recovered from the apple Eve gave Adam, woman was often a glorious strumpet.&lt;BR&gt;A. Kreymborg, Poetic Drama &lt;BR&gt;1941 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #14The fear of Friday the 13th..is thought to have its origins in the Bible, as it was on a Friday when Eve took a bite from the apple.&lt;BR&gt;, Daily Mail &lt;BR&gt;2006 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;</Question>
      <Answer>The round firm fruit (a pome) of any of various wild and cultivated trees of the genus Malus (see sense 4a), occurring in a wide variety of forms, colours, and flavours; esp. any of numerous cultivated kinds produced throughout the temperate zones of both hemispheres, typically having crisp white flesh and green, yellow, or red skin. &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Sense #6 &lt;BR&gt;According to post-biblical Christian tradition: the fruit of the tree of knowledge of good and evil eaten by Adam and Eve in the Garden of Eden in defiance of God's commandment; the forbidden fruit. Also used allusively. &lt;BR&gt;First use: Genesis B &lt;BR&gt;Part of speech: NN &lt;BR&gt;1000 -  &lt;BR&gt;</Answer>
      <SuperMemoReference>&amp;lt;H5 dir=ltr align=left&amp;gt;&amp;lt;Font size=&amp;quot;1&amp;quot; style=&amp;quot;color: transparent&amp;quot;&amp;gt; SuperMemo Reference:&amp;lt;/font&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;&amp;lt;FONT class=reference&amp;gt;Title:&amp;quot;My Test Quote&amp;quot; &amp;lt;br&amp;gt;Source: Oxford English Dictionary</SuperMemoReference>
    </Content>
  </SuperMemoElement>
  <SuperMemoElement>
    <ID>29</ID>
    <Title>apple_nn01-7</Title>
    <Type>Item</Type>
    <Content>
      <Question>Quotation #1Yn the calendars of Ianuar' Thu sclatt treys both set &amp; rere To graffy ther yn appyl &amp; pere.&lt;BR&gt;, Treat. Gardening &lt;BR&gt;1499 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #2Takyng a branche of a Beeche a foote thicke: and when they haue cutte it and bored it, they set in it the branches of the best Peare or Apple that they can geat.&lt;BR&gt;B. Googe, Foure Bks. Husbandry &lt;BR&gt;1577 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #3Oakes, Beeches, Chesnuts,..&amp;c. last longer than Apples, Peares, Plums, &amp;c.&lt;BR&gt;F. Bacon, Sylua Syluarum &lt;BR&gt;1626 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #4Graft..all kinds of Apples together, and also on Crabstocks.&lt;BR&gt;R. Austen, Treat. Fruit-trees &lt;BR&gt;1653 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #5You may also continue to prune Pears, Apples, and Plums until the middle or latter end of the next month.&lt;BR&gt;P. Miller, Gardeners Kalendar &lt;BR&gt;1731 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #6Fruit Trees thrive very well here, Apples Pears, Peaches, Plumbs Nectrans, Cherries Rasberries, &amp; Several other fine Fruit.&lt;BR&gt;W. Bartram, Trav. Georgia &amp; Florida &lt;BR&gt;1774 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #7The apple, though cultivated,..seems to be an exotic in southern Louisiana.&lt;BR&gt;W. Darby, Geogr. Descr. Louisiana &lt;BR&gt;1816 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #8The pear may be budded on the thorn, the mountain ash, or the apple, but the practice is not to be recommended.&lt;BR&gt;J. J. Black, Cultiv. Peach &amp; Pear &lt;BR&gt;1887 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #9A friend of mine..recently bought a tract of land in Georgia, with a view to planting apples.&lt;BR&gt;, Times &lt;BR&gt;1907 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #10The Wild Apple has not the pyramidal form of the Wild Pear.&lt;BR&gt;E. Step, Wayside &amp; Woodland Trees &lt;BR&gt;1940 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #11In 1883 Allen planted a mixture of Northern Spy, Baldwin and Rhode Island Greening apples.&lt;BR&gt;, Vermont Life &lt;BR&gt;1973 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #12Some temperate trees (like apples and horse chestnuts) are pollinated by animals.&lt;BR&gt;C. Tudge, Secret Life Trees &lt;BR&gt;2005 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;</Question>
      <Answer>The round firm fruit (a pome) of any of various wild and cultivated trees of the genus Malus (see sense 4a), occurring in a wide variety of forms, colours, and flavours; esp. any of numerous cultivated kinds produced throughout the temperate zones of both hemispheres, typically having crisp white flesh and green, yellow, or red skin. &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Sense #7 &lt;BR&gt;Any tree of the genus Malus (family Rosaceae); esp. any of the numerous varieties cultivated for their fruit, probably of hybrid origin and usually classified as M. domestica, having alternate serrated leaves and white blossom appearing in the spring, followed by fruit in late summer or autumn. Cf. apple tree n. &lt;BR&gt;First use: Treat. Gardening &lt;BR&gt;Part of speech: NN &lt;BR&gt;1499 -  &lt;BR&gt;</Answer>
      <SuperMemoReference>&amp;lt;H5 dir=ltr align=left&amp;gt;&amp;lt;Font size=&amp;quot;1&amp;quot; style=&amp;quot;color: transparent&amp;quot;&amp;gt; SuperMemo Reference:&amp;lt;/font&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;&amp;lt;FONT class=reference&amp;gt;Title:&amp;quot;My Test Quote&amp;quot; &amp;lt;br&amp;gt;Source: Oxford English Dictionary</SuperMemoReference>
    </Content>
  </SuperMemoElement>
  <SuperMemoElement>
    <ID>30</ID>
    <Title>apple_nn01-8</Title>
    <Type>Item</Type>
    <Content>
      <Question>Quotation #1What so euer fruite is to be eaten soft without, and hard within, is an Apple, and the contrary a Nut.&lt;BR&gt;B. Googe, Foure Bks. Husbandry &lt;BR&gt;1577 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #2An Apple, Pomum, is generally understood to be any fleshy Vessel containing more Seeds than one.&lt;BR&gt;J. Martyn, 1st Lect. Bot. &lt;BR&gt;1729 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #3Pomum or apple, which is a fleshy or pulpy kind of pericarpium: it contains in the middle a membraneous capsule..in which the seeds reside.&lt;BR&gt;R. Saumarez, New Syst. Physiol. &lt;BR&gt;1799 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;</Question>
      <Answer>The round firm fruit (a pome) of any of various wild and cultivated trees of the genus Malus (see sense 4a), occurring in a wide variety of forms, colours, and flavours; esp. any of numerous cultivated kinds produced throughout the temperate zones of both hemispheres, typically having crisp white flesh and green, yellow, or red skin. &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Sense #8 &lt;BR&gt;Botany. Any fruit having the structure of the apple; a pome. Obsolete. &lt;BR&gt;First use: Barnabe Googe &lt;BR&gt;Part of speech: NN &lt;BR&gt;1577 - 1799 &lt;BR&gt;This sense is obsolete &lt;BR&gt;</Answer>
      <SuperMemoReference>&amp;lt;H5 dir=ltr align=left&amp;gt;&amp;lt;Font size=&amp;quot;1&amp;quot; style=&amp;quot;color: transparent&amp;quot;&amp;gt; SuperMemo Reference:&amp;lt;/font&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;&amp;lt;FONT class=reference&amp;gt;Title:&amp;quot;My Test Quote&amp;quot; &amp;lt;br&amp;gt;Source: Oxford English Dictionary</SuperMemoReference>
    </Content>
  </SuperMemoElement>
  <SuperMemoElement>
    <ID>31</ID>
    <Title>apple_nn01-9</Title>
    <Type>Item</Type>
    <Content>
      <Question>Quotation #1He undertakes to Prove, that No Animal is generated but out of another Animal; Or some Plant Uncorrupted; as out of Oakapples, and severall prutuberancyes and Excresency's of Vegetables.&lt;BR&gt;J. Finch, Let. &lt;BR&gt;1668 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #2The fly injects her juices into the oak leaf, to raise an apple for hatching her young.&lt;BR&gt;A. Tucker, Light of Nature Pursued &lt;BR&gt;1768 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #3Bedeguars, commonly called ‘Soft apples’. This name is given to Galls which are covered with numerous close-set hairs or fibres.&lt;BR&gt;R. T. Hulme, Elements Med. Zool. &lt;BR&gt;1861 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #4Mecca galls, Dead Sea apples, Sodom apples, or mad apples..are occasionally imported from Bussarah.&lt;BR&gt;, Eng. Mech. &lt;BR&gt;1869 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #5The other..does not form galls or ‘apples’, but the teleutospore masses break out directly from the stem.&lt;BR&gt;, Bull. Torrey Bot. Club &lt;BR&gt;1900 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #6Similar galls of a beautiful rose color develop sometimes on cranberries; they are called ‘rose apples’.&lt;BR&gt;B. O. Dodge, Dis. &amp; Pests of Ornamental Plants &lt;BR&gt;1943 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #7The oak gall, or oak-apple, was the source of the ink in many an old master drawing that is now falling to pieces.&lt;BR&gt;, N.Y. Rev. Bks. &lt;BR&gt;2002 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;</Question>
      <Answer>The round firm fruit (a pome) of any of various wild and cultivated trees of the genus Malus (see sense 4a), occurring in a wide variety of forms, colours, and flavours; esp. any of numerous cultivated kinds produced throughout the temperate zones of both hemispheres, typically having crisp white flesh and green, yellow, or red skin. &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Sense #9 &lt;BR&gt;Chiefly with distinguishing word: a gall on the stem or leaf of a plant. &lt;BR&gt;First use: J. Finch &lt;BR&gt;Part of speech: NN &lt;BR&gt;1668 -  &lt;BR&gt;</Answer>
      <SuperMemoReference>&amp;lt;H5 dir=ltr align=left&amp;gt;&amp;lt;Font size=&amp;quot;1&amp;quot; style=&amp;quot;color: transparent&amp;quot;&amp;gt; SuperMemo Reference:&amp;lt;/font&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;&amp;lt;FONT class=reference&amp;gt;Title:&amp;quot;My Test Quote&amp;quot; &amp;lt;br&amp;gt;Source: Oxford English Dictionary</SuperMemoReference>
    </Content>
  </SuperMemoElement>
  <SuperMemoElement>
    <ID>32</ID>
    <Title>apple_nn01-10</Title>
    <Type>Item</Type>
    <Content>
      <Question>Quotation #1The wood of France may be divided into six classes..for the fourth, fir, beech, elm, pear tree, apple, cherry tree.&lt;BR&gt;, Edinb. Encycl. &lt;BR&gt;1815 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #2Pear tree is superior in toughness to apple, but the latter excels sycamore and chestnut in hardness.&lt;BR&gt;E. L. Tarbuck, Encycl. Pract. Carpentry &amp; Joinery &lt;BR&gt;1857 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #3The woods used for turning are roughly divided into hard and soft... The latter include walnut, mahogany, oak, beech..and apple.&lt;BR&gt;R. W. Cole,  &lt;BR&gt;1903 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #4When dry apple is one of the best woods for fuel.&lt;BR&gt;M. Hadfield, Brit. Trees &lt;BR&gt;1957 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #5He will use fruitwoods such as apple, plum, and, particularly, pear with its tight knit quality.&lt;BR&gt;, Woodworker &lt;BR&gt;1990 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;</Question>
      <Answer>The round firm fruit (a pome) of any of various wild and cultivated trees of the genus Malus (see sense 4a), occurring in a wide variety of forms, colours, and flavours; esp. any of numerous cultivated kinds produced throughout the temperate zones of both hemispheres, typically having crisp white flesh and green, yellow, or red skin. &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Sense #10 &lt;BR&gt;The wood of any of these trees, esp. used in woodworking. Cf. apple-wood n. at  compounds 1a(a). &lt;BR&gt;First use: Edinburgh Encyclopaedia &lt;BR&gt;Part of speech: NN &lt;BR&gt;1815 -  &lt;BR&gt;</Answer>
      <SuperMemoReference>&amp;lt;H5 dir=ltr align=left&amp;gt;&amp;lt;Font size=&amp;quot;1&amp;quot; style=&amp;quot;color: transparent&amp;quot;&amp;gt; SuperMemo Reference:&amp;lt;/font&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;&amp;lt;FONT class=reference&amp;gt;Title:&amp;quot;My Test Quote&amp;quot; &amp;lt;br&amp;gt;Source: Oxford English Dictionary</SuperMemoReference>
    </Content>
  </SuperMemoElement>
  <SuperMemoElement>
    <ID>33</ID>
    <Title>apple_nn01-11</Title>
    <Type>Item</Type>
    <Content>
      <Question>Quotation #1Apple and Pears, stairs.&lt;BR&gt;‘Ducange Anglicus’, Vulgar Tongue &lt;BR&gt;1857 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #2The clock on the apples and pears Gave the office for us to clear.&lt;BR&gt;, Sporting Times &lt;BR&gt;1892 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #3Bill an' Jack's gone up apples.&lt;BR&gt;J. R. Ware, Passing Eng. Victorian Era &lt;BR&gt;1909 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #4I soon shoved him down the Apples-and-pears.&lt;BR&gt;C. Mackenzie, Sinister St. &lt;BR&gt;1914 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #5One of the removal men asked him if a sofa was to go ‘up the apples’.&lt;BR&gt;J. G. Bennett, Witness &lt;BR&gt;1962 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #6I fell down the apples and landed on me bottle.&lt;BR&gt;, Forward &lt;BR&gt;2006 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;</Question>
      <Answer>The round firm fruit (a pome) of any of various wild and cultivated trees of the genus Malus (see sense 4a), occurring in a wide variety of forms, colours, and flavours; esp. any of numerous cultivated kinds produced throughout the temperate zones of both hemispheres, typically having crisp white flesh and green, yellow, or red skin. &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Sense #11 &lt;BR&gt;In full apple(s) and pears. Stairs. &lt;BR&gt;First use: ‘Ducange Anglicus’ &lt;BR&gt;Part of speech: NN &lt;BR&gt;1857 -  &lt;BR&gt;</Answer>
      <SuperMemoReference>&amp;lt;H5 dir=ltr align=left&amp;gt;&amp;lt;Font size=&amp;quot;1&amp;quot; style=&amp;quot;color: transparent&amp;quot;&amp;gt; SuperMemo Reference:&amp;lt;/font&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;&amp;lt;FONT class=reference&amp;gt;Title:&amp;quot;My Test Quote&amp;quot; &amp;lt;br&amp;gt;Source: Oxford English Dictionary</SuperMemoReference>
    </Content>
  </SuperMemoElement>
  <SuperMemoElement>
    <ID>34</ID>
    <Title>apple_nn01-12</Title>
    <Type>Item</Type>
    <Content>
      <Question>Quotation #1Those fellows are rotten apples.&lt;BR&gt;G. H. Devol, Forty Years Gambler on Mississippi &lt;BR&gt;1887 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #2There's no choosing between them rotten apples aft.&lt;BR&gt;F. Riesenberg, Under Sail &lt;BR&gt;1918 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #3Seen from this angle he looked what, in Bonaro's words he was,—‘a bad apple’.&lt;BR&gt;R. Dougherty, Commissioner &lt;BR&gt;1962 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #4The original ‘rotten apple’ is believed to have been a government agent.&lt;BR&gt;L. Kennedy, Brit. Intelligence Services in Action &lt;BR&gt;1980 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #5You are the one that's going to be stuck with the bill if you pick a bad apple.&lt;BR&gt;, Detroit News &lt;BR&gt;2006 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;</Question>
      <Answer>The round firm fruit (a pome) of any of various wild and cultivated trees of the genus Malus (see sense 4a), occurring in a wide variety of forms, colours, and flavours; esp. any of numerous cultivated kinds produced throughout the temperate zones of both hemispheres, typically having crisp white flesh and green, yellow, or red skin. &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Sense #12 &lt;BR&gt;rotten (also bad) apple: a negative or corrupting influence on others; a troublesome or despicable person; cf. phrases 2. &lt;BR&gt;First use: George H. Devol &lt;BR&gt;Part of speech: NN &lt;BR&gt;1887 -  &lt;BR&gt;</Answer>
      <SuperMemoReference>&amp;lt;H5 dir=ltr align=left&amp;gt;&amp;lt;Font size=&amp;quot;1&amp;quot; style=&amp;quot;color: transparent&amp;quot;&amp;gt; SuperMemo Reference:&amp;lt;/font&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;&amp;lt;FONT class=reference&amp;gt;Title:&amp;quot;My Test Quote&amp;quot; &amp;lt;br&amp;gt;Source: Oxford English Dictionary</SuperMemoReference>
    </Content>
  </SuperMemoElement>
  <SuperMemoElement>
    <ID>35</ID>
    <Title>apple_nn01-13</Title>
    <Type>Item</Type>
    <Content>
      <Question>Quotation #1I saw the apple in his throat rise and fall with the effort he made to swallow.&lt;BR&gt;S. J. Weyman, From Mem. Minister of France &lt;BR&gt;1895 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #2He looked..up and down the quay, a big apple bulging in his neck.&lt;BR&gt;J. Joyce, Ulysses &lt;BR&gt;1922 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #3I love all the world And the movement of the apple in your throat.&lt;BR&gt;C. Fry, Phoenix too Frequent &lt;BR&gt;1946 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #4Put one hand on the apple of the hound's throat and the other at the back of his head.&lt;BR&gt;, N.Y. Times Bk. Rev. &lt;BR&gt;1992 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;</Question>
      <Answer>The round firm fruit (a pome) of any of various wild and cultivated trees of the genus Malus (see sense 4a), occurring in a wide variety of forms, colours, and flavours; esp. any of numerous cultivated kinds produced throughout the temperate zones of both hemispheres, typically having crisp white flesh and green, yellow, or red skin. &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Sense #13 &lt;BR&gt;= Adam's apple n. 3. &lt;BR&gt;First use: Stanley Weyman &lt;BR&gt;Part of speech: NN &lt;BR&gt;1895 -  &lt;BR&gt;</Answer>
      <SuperMemoReference>&amp;lt;H5 dir=ltr align=left&amp;gt;&amp;lt;Font size=&amp;quot;1&amp;quot; style=&amp;quot;color: transparent&amp;quot;&amp;gt; SuperMemo Reference:&amp;lt;/font&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;&amp;lt;FONT class=reference&amp;gt;Title:&amp;quot;My Test Quote&amp;quot; &amp;lt;br&amp;gt;Source: Oxford English Dictionary</SuperMemoReference>
    </Content>
  </SuperMemoElement>
  <SuperMemoElement>
    <ID>36</ID>
    <Title>apple_nn01-14</Title>
    <Type>Item</Type>
    <Content>
      <Question>Quotation #1A gang of apple knockers strolled toward Mendon.., with Charles Dewey, the famous twirler.&lt;BR&gt;, Delphos (Ohio) Daily Herald &lt;BR&gt;1902 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #2Bert is playing a great game at third base and riding the old apple with wonderful severity.&lt;BR&gt;, Lincoln (Nebraska) Daily News &lt;BR&gt;1914 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #3Jo-jo belts the old apple right through a high window.&lt;BR&gt;D. Runyon, Collier's &lt;BR&gt;1931 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #4Just when I raised my arms to throw to second, the damn apple slipped out of my hand.&lt;BR&gt;R. A. Spears, NTC's Dict. Amer. Slang &lt;BR&gt;1989 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #5I'm glad Marbury is a Knick, but he sure does like to chuck that old apple, doesn't he?&lt;BR&gt;, Daily News (N.Y.) &lt;BR&gt;2004 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;</Question>
      <Answer>The round firm fruit (a pome) of any of various wild and cultivated trees of the genus Malus (see sense 4a), occurring in a wide variety of forms, colours, and flavours; esp. any of numerous cultivated kinds produced throughout the temperate zones of both hemispheres, typically having crisp white flesh and green, yellow, or red skin. &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Sense #14 &lt;BR&gt;U.S. colloquial. A baseball. Also more fully old apple. &lt;BR&gt;First use: Delphos (Ohio) Daily Herald &lt;BR&gt;Part of speech: NN &lt;BR&gt;1902 -  &lt;BR&gt;</Answer>
      <SuperMemoReference>&amp;lt;H5 dir=ltr align=left&amp;gt;&amp;lt;Font size=&amp;quot;1&amp;quot; style=&amp;quot;color: transparent&amp;quot;&amp;gt; SuperMemo Reference:&amp;lt;/font&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;&amp;lt;FONT class=reference&amp;gt;Title:&amp;quot;My Test Quote&amp;quot; &amp;lt;br&amp;gt;Source: Oxford English Dictionary</SuperMemoReference>
    </Content>
  </SuperMemoElement>
  <SuperMemoElement>
    <ID>37</ID>
    <Title>apple_nn01-15</Title>
    <Type>Item</Type>
    <Content>
      <Question>Quotation #1Colours: Peach, Apple, Apricot, Mauve, Fuchsia, Periwinkle.&lt;BR&gt;, Daily Mail &lt;BR&gt;1923 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #2Mini dress..coffee, apple, rose or delphinium print on green.&lt;BR&gt;, Guardian &lt;BR&gt;1970 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #3Five minutes later, the same outfit again—this time in tangerine, then apple, then citrus.&lt;BR&gt;, Independent &lt;BR&gt;1995 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #4The hottest summer colours..include the dusted pastels of violet, poppy, apple,.&lt;BR&gt;, Glebe &amp; Inner City News (Austral.) &lt;BR&gt;2000 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;</Question>
      <Answer>The round firm fruit (a pome) of any of various wild and cultivated trees of the genus Malus (see sense 4a), occurring in a wide variety of forms, colours, and flavours; esp. any of numerous cultivated kinds produced throughout the temperate zones of both hemispheres, typically having crisp white flesh and green, yellow, or red skin. &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Sense #15 &lt;BR&gt;A shade of green resembling the colour of a green apple. Cf. apple green n. adj. at  compounds 2. &lt;BR&gt;First use: Daily Mail &lt;BR&gt;Part of speech: NN &lt;BR&gt;1923 -  &lt;BR&gt;</Answer>
      <SuperMemoReference>&amp;lt;H5 dir=ltr align=left&amp;gt;&amp;lt;Font size=&amp;quot;1&amp;quot; style=&amp;quot;color: transparent&amp;quot;&amp;gt; SuperMemo Reference:&amp;lt;/font&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;&amp;lt;FONT class=reference&amp;gt;Title:&amp;quot;My Test Quote&amp;quot; &amp;lt;br&amp;gt;Source: Oxford English Dictionary</SuperMemoReference>
    </Content>
  </SuperMemoElement>
  <SuperMemoElement>
    <ID>38</ID>
    <Title>apple_nn01-16</Title>
    <Type>Item</Type>
    <Content>
      <Question>Quotation #1No. 1711 has the smart ‘apple bowl’. A sporty looker, and a mighty friendly, comfortable pipe.&lt;BR&gt;, Life &lt;BR&gt;1926 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #2The ‘Apple’ and the ‘Prince’ are examples of smaller, lighter bowls.&lt;BR&gt;A. Dunhill, Gentle Art of Smoking &lt;BR&gt;1954 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #3He lit a pipe, his largest shell-briar Apple.&lt;BR&gt;M. J. Bosse, Incident at Naha &lt;BR&gt;1972 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #4Hand-carved pipes..including..a roughneck with an apple bowl for $18.95.&lt;BR&gt;, Daily Oklahoman (Okla. City, Okla.) &lt;BR&gt;1994 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #5Apple, a classic pipe bowl shape resembling the roundness of an apple.&lt;BR&gt;D. Wright, Pipe Compan. &lt;BR&gt;2000 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;</Question>
      <Answer>The round firm fruit (a pome) of any of various wild and cultivated trees of the genus Malus (see sense 4a), occurring in a wide variety of forms, colours, and flavours; esp. any of numerous cultivated kinds produced throughout the temperate zones of both hemispheres, typically having crisp white flesh and green, yellow, or red skin. &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Sense #16 &lt;BR&gt;Also with capital initial. A round, apple-shaped bowl on a tobacco pipe (also more fully apple bowl); a tobacco pipe with such a bowl. &lt;BR&gt;First use: Life &lt;BR&gt;Part of speech: NN &lt;BR&gt;1926 -  &lt;BR&gt;</Answer>
      <SuperMemoReference>&amp;lt;H5 dir=ltr align=left&amp;gt;&amp;lt;Font size=&amp;quot;1&amp;quot; style=&amp;quot;color: transparent&amp;quot;&amp;gt; SuperMemo Reference:&amp;lt;/font&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;&amp;lt;FONT class=reference&amp;gt;Title:&amp;quot;My Test Quote&amp;quot; &amp;lt;br&amp;gt;Source: Oxford English Dictionary</SuperMemoReference>
    </Content>
  </SuperMemoElement>
  <SuperMemoElement>
    <ID>39</ID>
    <Title>apple_nn01-17</Title>
    <Type>Item</Type>
    <Content>
      <Question>Quotation #1‘I can't say,’ replied the poor apple.&lt;BR&gt;S. J. Perelman, Judge &lt;BR&gt;1928 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #2Boys do not meet with subdeb approval..are lumped together under such terms as..sad apples, meatballs,..and drips.&lt;BR&gt;, Life Mag. &lt;BR&gt;1941 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #3That's a different department; I don't hobnob with those apples.&lt;BR&gt;R. P. Davis, Pilot &lt;BR&gt;1976 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #4Leonard himself was a pretty tough apple.&lt;BR&gt;, Business Week &lt;BR&gt;2004 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;</Question>
      <Answer>The round firm fruit (a pome) of any of various wild and cultivated trees of the genus Malus (see sense 4a), occurring in a wide variety of forms, colours, and flavours; esp. any of numerous cultivated kinds produced throughout the temperate zones of both hemispheres, typically having crisp white flesh and green, yellow, or red skin. &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Sense #17 &lt;BR&gt;colloquial (chiefly U.S.). A person; a fellow, a guy. Usually with preceding adjective. &lt;BR&gt;First use: S. J. Perelman &lt;BR&gt;Part of speech: NN &lt;BR&gt;1928 -  &lt;BR&gt;</Answer>
      <SuperMemoReference>&amp;lt;H5 dir=ltr align=left&amp;gt;&amp;lt;Font size=&amp;quot;1&amp;quot; style=&amp;quot;color: transparent&amp;quot;&amp;gt; SuperMemo Reference:&amp;lt;/font&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;&amp;lt;FONT class=reference&amp;gt;Title:&amp;quot;My Test Quote&amp;quot; &amp;lt;br&amp;gt;Source: Oxford English Dictionary</SuperMemoReference>
    </Content>
  </SuperMemoElement>
  <SuperMemoElement>
    <ID>40</ID>
    <Title>apple_nn01-18</Title>
    <Type>Item</Type>
    <Content>
      <Question>Quotation #1Apple, the big town, the main stem, Harlem.&lt;BR&gt;C. Calloway, New Cab Calloway's Cat-ologue &lt;BR&gt;1939 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #2I'll write you from the apple.&lt;BR&gt;R. Ellison, Let. &lt;BR&gt;1953 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #3Both groups are symptomatic of the flood of young musicians storming into the Apple, abandoning studio sinecures and rock bands to play difficult improvisatory music.&lt;BR&gt;G. Giddins, Village Voice (N.Y.) &lt;BR&gt;1974 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #4Many of the city's most creative people in the 1970s (as now) were high IQ boys and girls from Smalltown who fled to the Apple.&lt;BR&gt;, Wall St. Jrnl. &lt;BR&gt;2005 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;</Question>
      <Answer>The round firm fruit (a pome) of any of various wild and cultivated trees of the genus Malus (see sense 4a), occurring in a wide variety of forms, colours, and flavours; esp. any of numerous cultivated kinds produced throughout the temperate zones of both hemispheres, typically having crisp white flesh and green, yellow, or red skin. &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Sense #18 &lt;BR&gt;U.S. slang (originally Jazz). Usually with capital initial. With the. Originally: Harlem. Hence later: New York City. Cf. Big Apple n. 4. &lt;BR&gt;First use: Cab Calloway &lt;BR&gt;Part of speech: NN &lt;BR&gt;1939 -  &lt;BR&gt;</Answer>
      <SuperMemoReference>&amp;lt;H5 dir=ltr align=left&amp;gt;&amp;lt;Font size=&amp;quot;1&amp;quot; style=&amp;quot;color: transparent&amp;quot;&amp;gt; SuperMemo Reference:&amp;lt;/font&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;&amp;lt;FONT class=reference&amp;gt;Title:&amp;quot;My Test Quote&amp;quot; &amp;lt;br&amp;gt;Source: Oxford English Dictionary</SuperMemoReference>
    </Content>
  </SuperMemoElement>
  <SuperMemoElement>
    <ID>41</ID>
    <Title>apple_nn01-19</Title>
    <Type>Item</Type>
    <Content>
      <Question>Quotation #1If everything is running smoothly ‘she's apples’.&lt;BR&gt;J. Binning, Target Area &lt;BR&gt;1943 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #2How's it going, Wally? Everything apples?&lt;BR&gt;T. A. G. Hungerford, Ridge &amp; River &lt;BR&gt;1952 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #3She felt their faint movements of relief and surprise. ‘Well,’ said Dixon, ‘that'd be a break. That'd be apples, that would.’&lt;BR&gt;R. Stow, To Islands &lt;BR&gt;1958 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #4Don't cry, Pru. Yuh go and see old Len Ramsbottom and betcha everything'll be apples.&lt;BR&gt;R. H. Morrieson, Scarecrow &lt;BR&gt;1963 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #5No one reckons it's ‘apples’ in the battle for Bass.&lt;BR&gt;, Sydney Morning Herald &lt;BR&gt;1975 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #6She's apples. Now you just lie back an' take it easy.&lt;BR&gt;R. Beilby, Gunner &lt;BR&gt;1977 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #7Apples &amp; Rice, nice. Generally shortened to the first element when describing something that is nice, e.g. ‘She's apples’. But used in full when used to describe something that isn't, e.g., ‘Oh, that's very apples and rice. I'm out of work and you're pregnant again.’&lt;BR&gt;R. Puxley, Cockney Rabbit &lt;BR&gt;1992 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #8Well, she's not much of a motor, but with a spray job and a new radiator she'll be apples!&lt;BR&gt;, Fast Forward &lt;BR&gt;1994 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;</Question>
      <Answer>The round firm fruit (a pome) of any of various wild and cultivated trees of the genus Malus (see sense 4a), occurring in a wide variety of forms, colours, and flavours; esp. any of numerous cultivated kinds produced throughout the temperate zones of both hemispheres, typically having crisp white flesh and green, yellow, or red skin. &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Sense #19 &lt;BR&gt;slang (chiefly Australian and New Zealand). Used to indicate a state of affairs regarded as good or satisfactory (or occasionally ironic the reverse). Chiefly in she's (also it's) apples and variants: everything is all right; things will be fine (see she pron.1 2a(e)). &lt;BR&gt;First use: J. Binning &lt;BR&gt;Part of speech: NN &lt;BR&gt;1943 -  &lt;BR&gt;</Answer>
      <SuperMemoReference>&amp;lt;H5 dir=ltr align=left&amp;gt;&amp;lt;Font size=&amp;quot;1&amp;quot; style=&amp;quot;color: transparent&amp;quot;&amp;gt; SuperMemo Reference:&amp;lt;/font&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;&amp;lt;FONT class=reference&amp;gt;Title:&amp;quot;My Test Quote&amp;quot; &amp;lt;br&amp;gt;Source: Oxford English Dictionary</SuperMemoReference>
    </Content>
  </SuperMemoElement>
  <SuperMemoElement>
    <ID>42</ID>
    <Title>apple_nn01-20</Title>
    <Type>Item</Type>
    <Content>
      <Question>Quotation #1Her 8-year-old boy criticized her 10-year-old daughter by calling her an ‘apple.’&lt;BR&gt;, Lawton (Okla.) Constit. &lt;BR&gt;1970 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #2The ‘apples’, who categorically reject the Indian culture they were born to, choose one side, the white.&lt;BR&gt;P. G. Allen, Sacred Hoop &lt;BR&gt;1986 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #3You ain't shit, you fucking apple.&lt;BR&gt;R. Hendrickson, Happy Trails &lt;BR&gt;1994 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #4I never saw money to do good things to Indians, it turns them into ‘Apples’—red on the outside, white in the middle.&lt;BR&gt;, Adrenalin &lt;BR&gt;2001 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;</Question>
      <Answer>The round firm fruit (a pome) of any of various wild and cultivated trees of the genus Malus (see sense 4a), occurring in a wide variety of forms, colours, and flavours; esp. any of numerous cultivated kinds produced throughout the temperate zones of both hemispheres, typically having crisp white flesh and green, yellow, or red skin. &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Sense #20 &lt;BR&gt;U.S. slang (derogatory). In North American Indian usage: a North American Indian regarded as espousing or adopting the values of white society or culture (see quot. 2001). Cf. Oreo n.1 2. &lt;BR&gt;First use: Lawton (Okla.) Constit. &lt;BR&gt;Part of speech: NN &lt;BR&gt;1970 -  &lt;BR&gt;</Answer>
      <SuperMemoReference>&amp;lt;H5 dir=ltr align=left&amp;gt;&amp;lt;Font size=&amp;quot;1&amp;quot; style=&amp;quot;color: transparent&amp;quot;&amp;gt; SuperMemo Reference:&amp;lt;/font&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;&amp;lt;FONT class=reference&amp;gt;Title:&amp;quot;My Test Quote&amp;quot; &amp;lt;br&amp;gt;Source: Oxford English Dictionary</SuperMemoReference>
    </Content>
  </SuperMemoElement>
  <SuperMemoElement>
    <ID>43</ID>
    <Title>apple_vb01-1</Title>
    <Type>Item</Type>
    <Content>
      <Question>Quotation #1For all the sort of them during the Summer throughout, never rest and give over, but either they floure, or they apple, or els be readie to bring foorth fruit.&lt;BR&gt;P. Holland, Hist. World &lt;BR&gt;1601 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #2To Pome or Apple, is said of the Heads of Artichokes when they grow round, and full shaped as an Apple. It is said also of Lettuce, &amp;c.&lt;BR&gt;J. Evelyn, Compl. Gard'ner &lt;BR&gt;1693 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #3Unless the Soil has some mixture of Sand the Turnips do not apple, as they call it: that is, do not bottom well.&lt;BR&gt;J. Morton, Nat. Hist. Northants. &lt;BR&gt;1712 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #4The Turneps grew 'till Christmas or longer, and appled well in gravelly or stony Grounds, because their Roots can't here enter so deep.&lt;BR&gt;W. Ellis, Mod. Husbandman &lt;BR&gt;1750 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #5The cabbage turnep is of two kinds; one apples above ground, and the other in it.&lt;BR&gt;C. Marshall, Introd. Knowl. &amp; Pract. Gardening &lt;BR&gt;1798 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #6Apple, to bottom at the roots. Turnips apple well, when the roots well, and assume a bulbous form.&lt;BR&gt;A. E. Baker, Gloss. Northants. Words &lt;BR&gt;1854 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #7The fine-leaved turnips that have escaped the fly, but have still to ‘apple’.&lt;BR&gt;P. H. Emerson, Birds, Beasts, &amp; Fishes Norfolk Broadland &lt;BR&gt;1895 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #8Potatoes and onions are said to apple when they develop properly. A dialect use.&lt;BR&gt;E. Gepp, Essex Dial. Dict. &lt;BR&gt;1923 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #9Me taters be n't applin' like they ed ough'ter.&lt;BR&gt;M. Carbery, Herts. Heritage &lt;BR&gt;1948 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #10Them blubs (bulbs) what we put awaay int' spring's gone an' appled nicely.&lt;BR&gt;J. M. Sims-Kimbrey, Wodds &amp; Doggerybaw: Lincs. Dial. Dict. &lt;BR&gt;1995 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;</Question>
      <Answer>intransitive. Of vegetables, flower buds, and esp. (in later use) root crops: to swell into a globular shape; to become shaped like an apple. &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Sense #1 &lt;BR&gt;intransitive. Of vegetables, flower buds, and esp. (in later use) root crops: to swell into a globular shape; to become shaped like an apple. &lt;BR&gt;First use: Philemon Holland &lt;BR&gt;Part of speech: VB &lt;BR&gt;1601 -  &lt;BR&gt;This is the main current sense &lt;BR&gt;</Answer>
      <SuperMemoReference>&amp;lt;H5 dir=ltr align=left&amp;gt;&amp;lt;Font size=&amp;quot;1&amp;quot; style=&amp;quot;color: transparent&amp;quot;&amp;gt; SuperMemo Reference:&amp;lt;/font&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;&amp;lt;FONT class=reference&amp;gt;Title:&amp;quot;My Test Quote&amp;quot; &amp;lt;br&amp;gt;Source: Oxford English Dictionary</SuperMemoReference>
    </Content>
  </SuperMemoElement>
  <SuperMemoElement>
    <ID>44</ID>
    <Title>apple_vb01-2</Title>
    <Type>Item</Type>
    <Content>
      <Question>Quotation #1The poor people supply themselves with very good fuel by gathering the fir-apples and rotten wood; you will sometimes see twenty children in my plantations appleing, as they call it.&lt;BR&gt;A. Young, Gen. View Agric. County Lincoln &lt;BR&gt;1799 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Quotation #2Going out appling is going out into the woods to collect fir cones for burning.&lt;BR&gt;J. M. Sims-Kimbrey, Wodds &amp; Doggerybaw: Lincs. Dial. Dict. &lt;BR&gt;1995 &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;</Question>
      <Answer>intransitive. Of vegetables, flower buds, and esp. (in later use) root crops: to swell into a globular shape; to become shaped like an apple. &lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;Sense #2 &lt;BR&gt;intransitive. To gather fir cones (see fir-apple n. at  fir n. compounds 2). rare. &lt;BR&gt;First use: Arthur Young &lt;BR&gt;Part of speech: VB &lt;BR&gt;1799 -  &lt;BR&gt;</Answer>
      <SuperMemoReference>&amp;lt;H5 dir=ltr align=left&amp;gt;&amp;lt;Font size=&amp;quot;1&amp;quot; style=&amp;quot;color: transparent&amp;quot;&amp;gt; SuperMemo Reference:&amp;lt;/font&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;&amp;lt;FONT class=reference&amp;gt;Title:&amp;quot;My Test Quote&amp;quot; &amp;lt;br&amp;gt;Source: Oxford English Dictionary</SuperMemoReference>
    </Content>
  </SuperMemoElement>
</SuperMemoCollection>